<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>June 1, 2018</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Mary Meeker's Internet Trends 2018</title>
    <quote>Among the conclusions: People are spending more on health care, meaning they might have to be more focused on value. Meeker asks: “Will market forces finally come to health care and drive prices lower for consumers?” Expect health care companies to offer more modern retail experiences, with convenient offices, digitized transactions and on-demand pharmacy services.</quote>
    <link>http://kpcbweb2.s3.amazonaws.com/files/121/INTERNET_TRENDS_REPORT_2018.pdf</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Invisible asymptotes</title>
    <quote>For me, in strategic planning, the question in building my forecast was to flush out what I call the invisible asymptote: a ceiling that our growth curve would bump its head against if we continued down our current path. It's an important concept to understand for many people in a company, whether a CEO, a product person, or, as I was back then, a planner in finance.</quote>
    <link>http://www.eugenewei.com/blog/2018/5/21/invisible-asymptotes/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>The Bill Gates Line</title>
    <quote>When that 15B happened a few months after Facebook Platform and Gates said something along the lines of, “...This isn’t a platform. A platform is when the economic value of everybody that uses it, exceeds the value of the company that creates it. Then it’s a platform.”</quote>
    <link>https://stratechery.com/2018/the-bill-gates-line/</link>
  </entry>
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>America’s Teens Are Choosing YouTube Over Facebook</title>
    <quote>Three years ago, Facebook was the dominant social media site among U.S. teens, visited by 71 percent of people in that magic, trendsetting demographic. Not anymore. Now only 51 percent of kids ages 13-17 use Facebook, according to Pew Research Center. The world’s largest social network is eclipsed in popularity by YouTube, Snapchat and Facebook Inc.-owned Instagram. </quote>
    <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-05-31/america-s-teens-are-choosing-youtube-over-facebook</link>
  </entry>
  
  
 <entry>
    <title>Roseanne Barr’s Ambien Defense Is Disputed: ‘Racism Is Not a Known Side Effect’</title>
    <quote>“People of all races, religions and nationalities work at Sanofi every day to improve the lives of people around the world,” the company, Sanofi U.S., said on Twitter. “While all pharmaceutical treatments have side effects, racism is not a known side effect of any Sanofi medication.”</quote>
    <link>https://twitter.com/SanofiUS/status/1001824999496404992</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
</feed>
