<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>May 27, 2016</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Regeneron Pharmaceuticals to Sponsor Science Talent Search</title>
    <quote>On Thursday, Regeneron Pharmaceuticals, a biotechnology company based in Tarrytown, N.Y., will announce that it is taking over sponsorship of the Science Talent Search with a 10-year, $100 million commitment to the high school competition.</quote>
    <link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/05/26/technology/regeneron-pharmaceuticals-to-sponsor-science-talent-search.html</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>what we can learn from Nike and Disney's approach to design</title>
    <quote>I think that probably is the emphasis—that design or design-led companies understand the human, the emotional side, the artful side, and that that has an important value.  A lot of these developments in wearables requires an environment that's networked and smart. I see that this is a very exciting new path for wearables, where it's not about just you and the wearable; it's about you, the wearable, and the environment you're in.</quote>
    <link>https://www.oreilly.com/ideas/max-burton-on-what-we-can-learn-from-nike-and-disneys-approach-to-design</link>
  </entry>
  
	<entry>
    <title>Fast.com</title>
    <quote>The ultimate dashboard: No click, essential information on your Internet speed</quote>
    <link>https://fast.com/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Who won Google VS Oracle? Developers won.</title>
    <quote>Well, if you’re developing software — or plan to in the future — this means that Google’s lawyers just steered you around a massive intellectual property minefield. They were able to prevent Oracle from setting a dangerous precedent: that a company could successfully sue you for writing your own functionally similar implementation of their APIs.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.freecodecamp.com/why-todays-victory-over-oracle-matters-so-much-to-developers-4e24b4a368b5#.d81zs1mrf</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Maker of Things</title>
    <quote>In a good bridge, I see the defiant end result of how some of my favorite engineering stories begin:
“I’m sure you can arrange an impressive line of people who say it’s impossible. I take personal joy in ignoring those who say no.”
“Yes, halfway through this project we’ll discover the impossible, but we know how to build through the impossible. Impossible is when we do our best work.”
“Trust me when I say that I can close my eyes and see the end result, and when you can see it, too, you will be amazed.”</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/@rands/the-maker-of-things-9c3f23b897a1#.1wcqb9vhv</link>
  </entry>
</feed>