<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>July 5, 2019</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>This changes everything for the DIY Diabetes Community</title>
    <quote>We the DIY #diabetes community declared #WeAreNotWaiting and, dammit, we'd do this ourselves. And now TidePool expressing the intent to put an Artificial Pancreas in the damn App Store - along with Angry Birds - WITH SUPPORT FOR WARRANTIED NEW BLE PUMPS. I could cry.</quote>
    <link>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/ThisChangesEverythingForTheDIYDiabetesCommunityTidePoolPartnersWithMedtronicAndDexcom.aspx</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Tracking and Visualizing Faces</title>
    <quote>Detect faces in a camera feed, overlay matching virtual content, and animate facial expressions in real-time.</quote>
    <link>https://developer.apple.com/documentation/arkit/tracking_and_visualizing_faces</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Formal Foundations of Serverless Computing</title>
    <quote>First, to ease reasoning about code, we present a simplified naive semantics of serverless execution and precisely characterize when the naive semantics and λΛ coincide. Second, we augment λΛ with a key-value store to allow reasoning about stateful serverless functions. Third, since a handful of serverless platforms support serverless function composition, we show how to extend λΛ with a composition language. We have implemented this composition language and show that it outperforms prior work.</quote>
    <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/1902.05870</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Accelerating Science: A Computing Research Agenda </title>
<quote>This calls for concerted research agenda aimed at: Development, analysis, integration, sharing, and simulation of algorithmic or information processing abstractions of natural processes, coupled with formal 
methods and tools for their analyses and simulation;Innovations in cognitive tools that augment 
and extend human intellect and partner with humans in all aspects of science.</quote>
    <link>https://cra.org/ccc/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/02/Accelerating-Science-Whitepaper-CCC-Final2.pdf</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Abigail Echo-Hawk on the art and science of 'decolonizing data'</title>
    <quote>The chief research officer of the Seattle Indian Health Board is creating programs and databases that are not based on Western concepts to better serve indigenous communities. </quote>
    <link>https://crosscut.com/2019/05/abigail-echo-hawk-art-and-science-decolonizing-data</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Amazon is 25 years old. What will the company’s next chapter look like?</title>
    <quote>Amazon turns 25 this week. Who would’ve thought back in 1994 that a tiny online bookseller might turn into a company that touches pretty much every aspect of our lives — what we buy, how we compute, how we watch movies and even get groceries.</quote>
    <link>https://www.marketplace.org/shows/marketplace-tech/amazon-is-25-years-old-what-will-companys-next-chapter-look-like/?</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
