<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>July 29, 2016</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Artificial Pancreas Is First To Raise $1 Million Under New Crowdfunding Rules</title>
    <quote>Beta Bionics, a startup created by Boston University biomedical engineer Ed Damiano, hit the benchmark Wednesday night after 775 members of the public put up an average of $1,300 each to back its idea for a new kind of pacemaker for diabetics. While some diabetics already use implanted sensors to read levels of glucose in their blood, Beta Bionics’s device, called the iLet, would also automatically pump insulin into the body when needed, creating a hands-off system.</quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/601999/artificial-pancreas-is-first-to-raise-1-million-under-new-crowdfunding-rules/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>IBM steps up efforts in fight against Zika</title>
    <quote>International Business Machines said on Wednesday it would provide its technology and resources to help track the spread of the Zika virus. Oswaldo Cruz Foundation (Fiocruz), a leading research institution affiliated with the Brazilian Ministry of Health, plans to use IBM’s technology to analyze information from official data about human travel patterns to anecdotal observations recorded on social media.</quote>
    <link>http://venturebeat.com/2016/07/28/ibm-steps-up-efforts-in-fight-against-zika/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How the most connected hospitals will use chatbots</title>
    <quote>Sure, chatbots are useful for service industries like hospitality and food delivery, but in health care? Some groups are testing the use of chatbots to retrieve medical information from within a messaging app. At first glance, that seems a bit impersonal, but a closer look reveals a wide range of use cases where bots could make your next visit to the hospital, doctor’s office, or pharmacy faster and more effective.</quote>
    <link>http://venturebeat.com/2016/07/28/how-the-most-connected-hospitals-will-use-chatbots/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Dollar Shave Club And The Disruption Of Everything</title>
    <quote>There was another product launch in 2006 that I’m sure no one at P&amp;G even noticed: Amazon Web Services. Even if they did notice, I doubt the executives focused on the Fusion launch appreciated that P&amp;G’s seemingly unassailable advantages were on the verge of declining precipitously. AWS made it easy and cheap to start an online company; YouTube, launched a year earlier, made it cheap and easy to share video; Facebook, launched in 2004, made it possible to spread said video to millions of people. All three came together with the 2011 founding of Dollar Shave Club and its 2012 launch with one of the best introductory videos of all time:</quote>
    <link>https://stratechery.com/2016/dollar-shave-club-and-the-disruption-of-everything/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Using Design Thinking to Embed Learning in Our Jobs</title>
    <quote>The telecomm company used design thinking to come up with a different approach: Rather than inject “training” into employees, it studied the job of a retail sales agent over the first nine months and developed a “journey map” showing what people need to know the first day, the first week, the first month, and then over the first few quarters.</quote>
    <link>https://hbr.org/2016/07/using-design-thinking-to-embed-learning-in-our-jobs</link>
  </entry>
  

</feed>
