<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>June 12, 2015</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Federal Panel Backs Approval of New Drug to Fight Heart Attacks</title>
    <quote>The powerful effects of the gene, PCSK9, that the drugs block, was discovered when researchers found people who were born with one copy mutated so it did not function. They seemed to be protect against heart disease. Then they found two young women with both copies knocked out. Both had astonishingly low cholesterol. One had an LDL level of 14 and the other’s was 15. That indicated that it might be safe to block the action of the gene with a drug and drive LDL levels very low. So far, it looks like just about everyone who takes the new drugs responds. LDL cholesterol levels plunge by about 40 to 65 percent, even if the starting level was achieved with a statin, the mainstay drug for cholesterol lowering first introduced in the late 1980s. Companies can make levels go even lower by increasing the dose of the new drugs.</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/1GwX2Lm</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Internet of Living Things</title>
    <quote>Making better day-to-day health decisions is by far the least costly way to avoid spending trillions on late-life care. Further, much of people’s health-related suffering can be significantly reduced or eliminated by making better lifestyle choices earlier in life. The business value is clear, but will wearables deliver on the promise to better inform and influence our health decisions?</quote>
    <link>http://radar.oreilly.com/2015/06/the-internet-of-living-things.html</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Oracle Sales Erode as Startups Embrace Souped-Up Free Software</title>
    <quote>Wagner’s company last year began shifting away from pricey products from Oracle and International Business Machines Corp., replacing them with open-source software, which is freely available and can be modified. Now, Wagner said the closely held company is converting virtually all of its operations to free database software.</quote>
    <link>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2015-06-11/oracle-sales-eroded-as-startups-embrace-souped-up-free-software</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What is Code?</title>
    <quote>A computer is a clock with benefits. They all work the same, doing second-grade math, one step at a time.</quote>
    <link>http://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2015-paul-ford-what-is-code/</link>
    <link>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/videos/2015-06-10/invisible-computer-code-runs-your-life</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The science behind Netflix’s first major redesign in four years</title>
    <quote>How Netflix is using a mountain of data to get you to watch more stuff</quote>
    <link>http://www.theverge.com/2015/5/22/8642359/the-science-behind-the-new-netflix-design</link>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
