<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>March 18, 2016</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How Gut Bacteria Are Shaking Up Cancer Research</title>
    <quote>"Five years ago, if you had asked me about bacteria in your gut playing an important role in your systemic immune response, I probably would have laughed it off," Daniel Chen, head of cancer immunotherapy research at Roche’s Genentech division</quote>
    <link>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2016-03-14/how-gut-bacteria-are-shaking-up-cancer-research</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Handful of Biologists Went Rogue and Published Directly to Internet</title>
    <quote>For most of the history of organized scientific research, the limitations of technology made print journals the chief means of disseminating scientific results. But some #ASAPbio advocates argue that since the rise of the Internet, biologists have been abdicating their duty to the public — which pays for most academic research — by not sharing results as quickly and openly as possible.</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/1XsJPHp</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Vic Gundotra, Former Google+ Boss, Is Building a Heart Monitor for the Apple Watch</title>
    <quote>AliveCor, a startup that builds heart-monitoring sensors for smartphones, is building sensors for another mobile device: The Apple Watch. AliveCor is also putting out a new app replete with speech-recognition features that, paired with the watch sensor, the startup hopes will replace the cumbersome, expensive devices for patients with pressing heart conditions.</quote>
    <link>https://recode.net/2016/03/16/medical-startup-alivecor-bakes-heart-monitor-into-apple-watch-poaches-two-googlers-for-exec-team/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Amazon Tax</title>
    <quote>If Amazon wanted to stimulate creativity among its developers, it shouldn’t try to guess what kind of services they might want; such guesses would be based on patterns of the past. Instead, it should be creating primitives — the building blocks of computing — and then getting out of the way.</quote>
    <quote>Steven Sinofsky is fond of noting that organizations tend to ship their org chart, and while I began by suggesting Amazon was duplicating the AWS model, it turns out that the AWS model was in many respects a representation of Amazon itself (just as the iPhone in many respects reflects Apple’s unitary organization): create a bunch of primitives, get out of the way, and take a nice skim off the top.</quote>
    <link>https://stratechery.com/2016/the-amazon-tax/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
</feed>
