<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>July 22, 2016</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hotlines Faster Than Hospitals in Pinpointing Dengue, Study Says</title>
    <quote>Calls to public health hotlines can predict dengue fever outbreaks two or three weeks earlier than local hospitals can confirm them, according to a new study from Pakistan. The study looked at 300,000 calls to a health hotline in Lahore over two years. By asking callers to describe their symptoms and give their addresses, operators were able to pinpoint which districts in the city were having dengue outbreaks.</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/29KDEf7</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The DIY diabetes kit that's keeping us alive </title>
    <quote>"I was sending a seven-year-old to school with a drug that could kill him," says Alistair Samuelson, whose son George, now nine, has type 1 diabetes. Frustrated with traditional monitoring and its risks, Mr Samuelson and George have since joined a growing group of T1 sufferers who are building their own solutions to manage their diabetes - even though they come with their own uncertainties.</quote>
    <link>http://www.bbc.com/news/technology-36711994</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Emotional Design. Adding a little cherry on top of your product’s UX.</title>
    <quote>Last year I took part in a workshop about emotional intelligence with a group of software engineers. Engineers believe in systematic thinking, algorithms and analytics. They don’t believe in emotions. When the workshop’s instructor asked if psychology was a science, they giggled. That’s a very common reaction. Emotional design is not a design discipline, like graphic design or car design. It’s also not a step in the UX design process, like interaction or visual design. Emotional design is a layer, a perspective. It should be sprinkled on top of the whole experience. It’s the little cherry on top, the extra mile that makes people love a product.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/outsystems-experts/emotional-design-adding-a-little-cherry-on-top-of-your-products-ux-bf8816c3b40d#.k55uu1ncb</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Apple Scores GlaxoSmithKline Study in Key Test of Health Apps</title>
    <quote>GlaxoSmithKline Plc has started a rheumatoid arthritis study using Apple Inc.’s ResearchKit, marking the first time a drugmaker has used the health system for the iPhone to conduct clinical research.</quote>
    <link>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2016-07-15/apple-scores-glaxosmithkline-study-in-key-test-of-health-apps</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Microsoft Stream</title>
    <quote>Engage and inspire your workforce. Upload and share videos across your organization to improve communication, participation, and learning.</quote>
    <link>https://stream.microsoft.com/en-us/</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
