<feed>
<title>Friday Feed</title>
<date>June 5, 2015</date>


<entry>
	<title>Life After Cancer: How the iPhone Helped Me Achieve a Healthier Lifestyle</title>
	<quote>Last year, I decided to put an end to my sedentary, lazy lifestyle. I was fed up: I gained weight because I didn't pay attention to what I was eating or drinking; I didn't have enough breath for two flights of stairs; I might have beaten cancer, but I wasn't living a healthy lifestyle. I was wasting the second opportunity I was given and I felt ashamed of myself for not valuing it enough. I turned to the iPhone for help.</quote>
	<link>http://www.macstories.net/stories/life-after-cancer-how-the-iphone-helped-me-achieve-a-healthier-lifestyle/</link>
</entry>

<entry>
	<title>This Cancer Doctor Is Leading the Attack on Astronomical Drug Prices</title>
	<quote>As the one-year cost of cancer drugs edges up to $200,000 per patient, a top doctor from Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center used his speech before a massive gathering of colleagues to call for limits on the cost of cancer therapies. “These drugs cost too much,”</quote>
	<link>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2015-06-01/this-cancer-doctor-is-leading-the-attack-on-astronomical-drug-prices</link>
</entry>

<entry>
	<title>The first secret of design is ... noticing</title>
	<quote>As human beings, we get used to "the way things are" really fast. But for designers, the way things are is an opportunity ... Could things be better? How? In this funny, breezy talk, the man behind the iPod and the Nest thermostat shares some of his tips for noticing — and driving — change.</quote>
	<link>http://www.ted.com/talks/tony_fadell_the_first_secret_of_design_is_noticing</link>
</entry>


<entry>
	<title>Slack’s $2.8 Billion Dollar Secret Sauce</title>
	<quote>When he pulled back the curtain and shared their early prototype on day one, it looked like a hacked together version of IRC in the browser. Barebones and stark. Just six weeks later, we had done some of the best work of our careers. So, how did we get from hacky browser IRC to the Slack we all know and love?</quote>
	<link>https://medium.com/@awilkinson/slack-s-2-8-billion-dollar-secret-sauce-5c5ec7117908</link>
</entry>

<entry>
	<title>Hello World: Windows 10 Available on July 29</title>
	<quote>Through the feedback and testing of over four million Windows Insiders, we’ve made great progress on Windows 10 and we’re nearly ready to deliver this free upgrade to all of our Windows customers*</quote>
	<link>http://blogs.windows.com/bloggingwindows/2015/06/01/hello-world-windows-10-available-on-july-29/</link>
	<link>https://youtu.be/Wwc5jKc-EgE</link>
</entry>


</feed>
