<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>January 27, 2017</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Predicting Medical AI in 2017</title>
    <quote>We will see the quantity of phase I research double in 2017, We will see several (3-5) large phase II AI trials published in the medical literature, We won’t see any complete phase III trials in 2017</quote>
    <link>https://lukeoakdenrayner.wordpress.com/2016/12/31/predicting-medical-ai-in-2017/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Machine Vision Helps Spot New Drug Treatments</title>
    <quote>Recursion uses software to read out the results of high-throughput screening, which automates drug testing in cells. That isn’t a new idea, but Recursion uses algorithms that inspect cells at an unusual level of detail. The software measures a thousand features of a cell, such as the size and shape of its nucleus or the distance between different internal compartments.</quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/603384/machine-vision-helps-spot-new-drug-treatments/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Stop Checking Email So Often</title>
    <quote>we observed a significant reduction in stress when they checked email less frequently. How much less stressed did people feel during their email-minimizing week compared with their email-maximizing week? The reduction in stress was about as large as the benefit people get from learning relaxation techniques (e.g., taking deep breaths, visualizing peaceful imagery). In other words, cutting back on email might reduce stress as much as picturing yourself swimming in the warm waters of a tropical island several times a day.</quote>
    <link>https://nyti.ms/2kmN6ir</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>10 Ways UX Research Is Changing</title>
    <quote>Pull based, just-in-time research, Research is validated continuously, Less linear product development process, Less research in a vacuum, Facilitation, Lightweight presentations, Using both quantitative and qualitative data, Experiment Design, A bigger research library to manage, Evolving role of product managers.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/@johnpcutler/10-ways-ux-research-is-changing-62fde944672#.c1almbgft</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>This 100-Year-Old Dutch Movement Shaped Web Design Today</title>
    <quote>Primary colors, clean lines, asymmetrical simplicity: You might recognize them from Google, but they come from De Stijl.</quote>
    <link>This 100-Year-Old Dutch Movement Shaped Web Design Today</link>
  </entry>
  


  
</feed>
