<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>June 11, 2021</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>I helped pioneer UX design. What I see today disturbs me</title>
    <quote>Instead of challenging teams to stretch their thinking to address deeper and subtler user needs, product design practices have become increasingly less insight-driven. UX processes in many organizations these days amount to little more than “UX Theatre”</quote>
    <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90642462/i-helped-pioneer-ux-design-what-i-see-today-horrifies-me</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Good internet service is still a luxury in the US</title>
    <quote>Lower-income Americans are way less likely to have broadband.</quote>
    <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/22463131/pew-broadband-internet-income-inequality</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>How A New Team Of Feds Hacked The Hackers And Got Colonial Pipeline's Ransom Back</title>
    <quote>The Justice Department has assembled a new task force to confront ransomware after what officials say was the most costly year on record for the crippling cyberattacks. It managed to recover $2.3 million of the ransom paid by Colonial Pipeline in an attack earlier this year, the department announced Monday.</quote>
    <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/06/08/1004223000/how-a-new-team-of-feds-hacked-the-hackers-and-got-colonial-pipelines-bitcoin-bac</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What Really Happened When Google Ousted Timnit Gebru</title>
    <quote>She was a star engineer who warned that messy AI can spread racism. Google brought her in. Then it forced her out. Can Big Tech take criticism from within?</quote>
    <link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-timnit-gebru-ai-what-really-happened/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Work from Home &amp; Productivity: Evidence from Personnel &amp; Analytics Data on it Professionals</title>
    <quote>These findings suggest that communication and coordination costs increased substantially
during WFH, and constituted an important source of the decline in productivity. Employees
with children living at home increased hours worked more than those without children at
home, and suffered a bigger decline in productivity than those without children.</quote>
    <link>https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=3846680</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
</feed>
