<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>August 5, 2016</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Setting the Body’s ‘Serial Killers’ Loose on Cancer</title>
    <quote>The patient’s T-cells, the soldiers of the immune system, are extracted from the patient’s blood, then genetically engineered to recognize and destroy cancer. The redesigned cells are multiplied in the laboratory, and millions or billions of them are put back into the patient’s bloodstream, set loose like a vast army of tumor assassins. This is an unusual pharmaceutical — a drug that is alive and can multiply once inside the body. Dr. June calls these cells “serial killers.” A single one can destroy up to 100,000 cancer cells.</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/2ad5qFR</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Harnessing the Immune System to Fight Cancer</title>
    <quote>Harnessing the immune system to fight cancer, long a medical dream, is becoming a reality. Remarkable stories of tumors melting away and terminal illnesses going into remissions that last years — backed by solid data — have led to an explosion of interest and billions of dollars of investments in the rapidly growing field of immunotherapy. Pharmaceutical companies, philanthropists and the federal government’s “cancer moonshot” program are pouring money into developing treatments. Medical conferences on the topic are packed.</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/2aRJLQC</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Moore’s Law Is About to Get Weird</title>
    <quote>his information and the hardware that processes it can take an almost endless variety of physical forms. Over nearly two centuries, scientists and engineers have experimented with designs that use mechanical gears, chemical reactions, fluid flows, light, DNA, living cells, and synthetic cells.</quote>
    <link>http://nautil.us/issue/21/information/moores-law-is-about-to-get-weird</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Die Dashboards Die! Why Conversations Will Reinvent Software</title>
    <quote>In years to come, conversations will breathe new life into software — particularly the boring enterprise tools millions of knowledge workers begrudgingly use every day. Conversational user interfaces (CUIs) work because of our familiarity with messaging. Even the most technically complex interactions can look as simple as getting an SMS text when presented as a conversation. Dashboards today pump out data and expect the user to do the rest. However, tomorrow’s conversational interfaces will surface insights first, then back them up with data as needed.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/behavior-design/die-dashboards-die-why-conversations-will-reinvent-software-a632880d5465#.khvc4iy8r</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>There’s a simple way to have meetings that result in something meaningful</title>
    <quote>But Claudia Williams, a senior policy advisor for OSTP and one of the leaders of the workshop, did something ingenious as the meeting came to a close. She set aside time for everyone in the room to share an appreciation, extend an offer, or make an ask. People raised their hands and spoke ad-hoc. No one had anything prepared but a few people expressed gratitude, some made asks, and many more put forth offers.</quote>
    <link>http://qz.com/749448/theres-a-simple-way-to-have-meetings-that-result-in-something-meaningful/</link>
  </entry>

</feed>
