<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>May 1, 2020</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Suddenly Remote Playbook</title>
    <quote>This has been an extraordinary moment for remote work. Entire populations have been forced to work from home, proving remote infrastructure viable on a massive scale. Now, companies of all sizes ask: “How do you do distributed work the right way? How do you run a remote operation with the most efficiency?”</quote>
    <link>https://www.toptal.com/remote-work-playbook</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Coronavirus Is Rewriting Our Imaginations</title>
    <quote>What felt impossible has become thinkable. The spring of 2020 is suggestive of how much, and how quickly, we can change as a civilization.</quote>
    <link>https://www.newyorker.com/culture/annals-of-inquiry/the-coronavirus-and-our-future</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Recipes for building an open-domain chatbot</title>
    <quote>Human evaluations show our best models are superior to existing approaches in multi-turn dialogue in terms of engagingness and humanness measurements. </quote>
    <link>https://parl.ai/projects/blender/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>THe Design Squiggle</title>
    <quote>The Design Squiggle is a simple illustration of the design process. The journey of researching, uncovering insights, generating creative concepts, iteration of prototypes and eventually concluding in one single designed solution. </quote>
    <link>https://thedesignsquiggle.com/</link>
  </entry>
  

  <entry>
    <title>The Anti-Amazon Alliance</title>
    <quote>The problem is that the gravitational pull of an integrated offering like Amazon.com is nearly impossible to resist; witness how Windows once spoiled Microsoft services, and Android Google services. Perhaps it was too much to expect Amazon to be any different — or, to put it another way, maybe Amazon always was an integrator, just at a far grander scale.</quote>
    <link>https://stratechery.com/2020/the-anti-amazon-alliance/</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
