<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>July 24, 2015</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Drug Prices Soar, Prompting Calls for Justification</title>
    <quote>Three of the bills require disclosures for drugs costing $10,000 or more per year. The others have different criteria. Besides development costs, some of the bills would require disclosure of the costs of manufacturing, marketing and advertising. At least some of the bills also ask for a history of price increases, the profit attributable to the drug and how much a company spends in providing financial assistance to patients using the drug.</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/1LvJykL</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Living With Cancer: Curses and Blessings</title>
    <quote>There can be no simple answer, but I seek clues in works of art created by terminal cancer patients. Take, for example, the paintings of Hollis Sigler, which have been shown in hospitals across the country and collected in the volume “Hollis Sigler’s Breast Cancer Journal.”</quote>
    <link>http://well.blogs.nytimes.com/2015/07/16/living-with-cancer-curses-and-blessings/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why you need design</title>
    <quote>Yet when we build websites or apps, we often wait until the last minute to bring in designers to “apply” design, or look and feel. This is akin to baking a cake and then hiring a baker to make it taste good.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/@monteiro/why-you-need-design-77dce41e0e0c</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Horrible Pain and Awesome Opportunity of Tech Blind Spots</title>
    <quote>You’ll hear this same dismissal — “We took care of that already” — like a choral refrain in the early-day ballads of startup legend. It’s there in the sagas of Paypal and Facebook, Dropbox and Slack. None of these were “first movers”; they all entered markets that tech investors and pundits had declared sewn up.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/backchannel/the-biggest-tech-problems-so-obvious-we-aren-t-fixing-them-87f4b708a7f1</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Want a Better Pitch? Watch This.</title>
    <quote>That’s because Musk does five things right that you should emulate in every pitch you ever make to anybody. And you should do them in this order:</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/firm-narrative/want-a-better-pitch-watch-this-328b95c2fd0b</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
  	<title>Making Architecture Matter</title>
  	<quote>Thoughtwork's Martin Fowler stressed the importance of software architecture: "If we don’t keep good architecture, we are...stealing from our customers."</quote>
  	<link>https://youtu.be/DngAZyWMGR0</link>
  </entry>
  

</feed>
