<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>June 8, 2018</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Cost of Developers</title>
    <quote>Developers can be quite expensive indeed!</quote>
    <link>https://stratechery.com/2018/the-cost-of-developers/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>The 6 biggest highlights from Apple WWDC 2018</title>
    <quote>(1) iOS 12 Gets In On Time Well Spent, 
(2) More Visual Fun On iOS 12, Siri Gets An Update... But Not Quite The One You’re Looking For, 
(3) MacOS Mojave Announced
(4) watchOS 5 Takes On Fitbit,
(5) Dolby Atmos Arrives On Apple TV 4K, </quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2018/6/4/17410820/apple-wwdc-summary-updates-highlights-news-2018</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Infrastructure for Usable Machine Learning: The Stanford DAWN Project</title>
    <quote>Despite incredible recent advances in machine learning, building machine learning applications remains prohibitively time-consuming and expensive for all but the best-trained, best-funded engineering organizations. This expense comes not from a need for new and improved statistical models but instead from a lack of systems and tools for supporting end-to-end machine learning application development, from data preparation and labeling to productionization and monitoring. In this document, we outline opportunities for infrastructure supporting usable, end-to-end machine learning applications in the context of the nascent DAWN (Data Analytics for What’s Next) project at Stanford.</quote>
    <link>https://arxiv.org/pdf/1705.07538.pdf</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>AI at Google: our principles</title>
    <quote>We recognize that such powerful technology raises equally powerful questions about its use. How AI is developed and used will have a significant impact on society for many years to come. As a leader in AI, we feel a deep responsibility to get this right. So today, we’re announcing seven principles to guide our work going forward. These are not theoretical concepts; they are concrete standards that will actively govern our research and product development and will impact our business decisions.</quote>
    <link>https://blog.google/topics/ai/ai-principles/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Apple's Plans To Bring Artificial Intelligence To Your Phone</title>
    <quote>At Apple’s Worldwide Developer Conference on Monday, Federighi revealed the next phase of his plan to enliven the app store with AI. It’s a tool called Create ML that’s something like a set of training wheels for building machine learning models in the first place. In a demo, training an image-recognition algorithm to distinguish different flavors of ice cream was as easy as dragging and dropping a folder containing a few dozen images and waiting a few seconds.</quote>
    <link>https://www.wired.com/story/apples-plans-to-bring-artificial-intelligence-to-your-phone/?mbid=email_onsiteshare</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
