<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>April 10, 2020</date>
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hospitals Deploy AI Tools to Detect COVID-19 on Chest Scans</title>
    <quote>Over the past week, companies around the world announced a flurry of AI-based systems to detect COVID-19 on chest CT or X-ray scans. Already, these deep learning tools are being used in hospitals to screen mild cases, triage new infections, and monitor advancing disease.</quote>
    <link>https://spectrum.ieee.org/the-human-os/biomedical/imaging/hospitals-deploy-ai-tools-detect-covid19-chest-scans</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Stanford to offer free online CS class during pandemic</title>
    <quote>“This is a really tough time for a lot of people,” Piech said. “And we thought that for some people stuck at home, learning to code is not just reasonable, but might be a great thing to do; that could be students with intellectual curiosity or adults who want a new skill for the workforce.”</quote>
    <link>https://www.stanforddaily.com/2020/03/31/stanford-to-offer-free-online-cs-class-during-pandemic/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>This Agency Guy Built an A.I. Clone to Attend Zoom Meetings for Him</title>
    <quote>"The idea of a digital twin of yourself came up," he says. "We also knew we wanted to do something to bring a smile to people, and the digital twin that awkwardly handled your Zoom meetings using overused meeting jargon could do just that. At the worst, it could stall for you while you take a bio-break, and ideally it would handle your entire meeting from 'Hello' to 'Bye' without anyone noticing. Oh, but they noticed."</quote>
    <link>https://musebycl.io/index.php/makers/agency-guy-built-ai-clone-attend-zoom-meetings-him</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Typography in Album Artwork: From Groovy Typefaces to Handwritten Calligraphy</title>
    <quote>They say you aren’t supposed to judge a book by its cover and it’s also true that you can’t judge a song based on its album art. </quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/nightingale/typography-in-album-artwork-from-groovy-typefaces-to-handwritten-calligraphy-5cab22d6fa0d</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>COBOL Programmers Needed</title>
    <quote>The governor of New Jersey just put out the call on live TV that he is desperate for Cobol programmers right now.</quote>
    <link>https://twitter.com/manicode/status/1246497036389793792</link>
  </entry>
  
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
</feed>
