<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>April 2, 2021</date>

  <entry>
    <title>The Robots Are Coming For Your Office</title>
    <quote>If you have the kind of job that involves sitting in front of a computer using the same software the same way every day, automation is coming for you. It won’t be cool or innovative or even work all that well — it’ll just be cheaper, faster, and less likely to complain.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2021/3/23/22344938/kevin-roose-robotic-automation-future-rpa</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Louvre has digitized 482,000 artworks</title>
    <quote>The Collections database consists of entries for more than 480,000 works in the Musée du Louvre and Musée National Eugène-Delacroix. Updated on a daily basis, it is the result of the continuous research and documentation efforts carried out by teams of experts from both museums.</quote>
    <link>https://collections.louvre.fr/en/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>What FaceID really looks like</title>
    <quote>How the Face ID (or ‘TrueDepth’) sensor housed the iPhone “notch” works. Here’s FaceID in action, shot in infrared: (see also: https://lux.camera/iphone-12-camera-review/)</quote>
    <link>https://twitter.com/sdw/status/1377380815428939778</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Think You Can Tell the Difference Between Human and AI? Take This Test</title>
    <quote>What makes a painting uniquely human? Is music generated by artificial intelligence really that different from what a human makes? Can you tell when a machine learning program has created the image you’re looking at?</quote>
    <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkdj8g/think-you-can-tell-the-difference-between-human-and-ai-take-this-test</link>
  </entry>

   <entry>
    <title>Siri gets two more male and female voices</title>
    <quote>Hi, I'm Siri, choose the voice you'd like me to use</quote>
    <link>https://twitter.com/i/status/1377410922147274754</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
