<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>September 18, 2015</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Peter Thiel Explains Biotech Investing Rationale: Get Rid of Randomness</title>
    <quote>They convinced me there is a surprising amount that has gone wrong with the cancer cell lines people have been studying. This framework of getting rid of probabilistic contingencies leads us to think it is quite a valuable company and is quite an unusual company. It runs counter to so much of the culture of the way biotech gets done.</quote>
    <link>http://www.technologyreview.com/news/541226/peter-thiel-explains-biotech-investing-rationale-get-rid-of-randomness/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why Google Is Going All In On Diabetes</title>
    <quote>Google Life Sciences earlier this week announced a partnership with Sanofi, maker of an insulin inhaler and a slew of other products for people with diabetes. Google is also working with Johnson &amp; Johnson on surgical robots, Biogen on potential treatments for multiple sclerosis and Novartis and Dexcom on diabetes-related projects.

But the diabetes market appears to be the primary focus. Data and analytics is Google's area of expertise, and as Miller puts it, diabetes management is fundamentally an "information problem."</quote>
    <link>http://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2015/09/06/437570402/why-google-is-going-all-in-on-diabetes</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>How to Design a Pitch Deck: Lessons from a Seasoned Founder</title>
    <quote>The best approach is to weave a compelling, 3 minute story about what’s wrong with the world, what the inevitable solution is, how your product happens to be that solution, and why your company will succeed.</quote>
    <link>https://blog.growth.supply/how-to-design-a-pitch-deck-lessons-from-a-seasoned-founder-c816d1ae7272</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>New York Mayor to Announce 10-Year Deadline to Offer Computer Science to All Students</title>
    <quote>To ensure that every child can learn the skills required to work in New York City’s fast-growing technology sector, Mayor Bill de Blasio will announce on Wednesday that within 10 years all of the city’s public schools will be required to offer computer science to all students.</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/1UTzeZ6</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>UX Research Methods</title>
    <quote>I’ve outlined several of the most common user experience research methods which are most prevalent and relevant today. I’ve weighed pros and cons, and included high-level cost breakdowns.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/@jackietanner/ux-research-methods-acb80b141bdc</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
