<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>September 30, 2016</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>A High-Stakes Bet: Turning Google Assistant Into a ‘Star Trek’ Computer</title>
    <quote>But the Assistant also presents Google with a delicious opportunity. The “Star Trek” computer is no metaphor. The company believes that machine learning has advanced to the point that it is now possible to build a predictive, all-knowing, superhelpful and conversational assistant of the sort that Captain Kirk relied on to navigate the stars.</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/2cCsKxX</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella on how AI will transform his company</title>
    <quote>“With Office 365, we are not just moving to the cloud,” Nadella said. “The most profound shift is in the fact that the data underneath the applications of Office 365 is exposed in a graph structure. And in a trusted, private-preserving way, we can reason over this data and create intelligence. That’s really the profound shift in Office 365.”</quote>
    <link>https://techcrunch.com/2016/09/26/microsoft-ceo-satya-nadella-on-how-ai-will-transform-his-company/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Snapchat Spectacles And The Future Of Wearables</title>
    <quote>Much more significantly, though, Spectacles have the critical ecosystem and use case components in place: Snapchat has over 150 million daily active users sending over a billion snaps a day and watching an incredible 10 billion videos. All of them are exclusive to Snapchat. Making it easier to add videos — memories,</quote>
    <link>https://stratechery.com/2016/snapchat-spectacles-and-the-future-of-wearables/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>People are digging through their trash and reusing Target’s well-designed prescription pill bottles</title>
    <quote>The celebrated red “ClearRx” design solved many common complaints with the standard plastic vials that use the old “Palm N’ Turn” cap. Target’s bottles were easier to open while remaining child-proof; they had a color ring for each member of the family to avoid confusion among medications; and perhaps most importantly, it had a clear, easy-to-read label with the text sized appropriately for aging eyes. Target touted the bottles as an avatar for its design-minded brand ethos and continued to refine its design with enhancements introduced in 2012.</quote>
    <link>http://qz.com/796794/clearrx-people-are-digging-through-their-trash-to-save-targets-well-designed-prescription-pill-bottles/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Aetna to Transform Members’ Consumer Health Experience Using iPhone, iPad and Apple Watch</title>
    <quote>Beginning this fall, Aetna will make Apple Watch available to select large employers and individual customers during open enrollment season, and Aetna will be the first major health care company to subsidize a significant portion of the Apple Watch cost, offering monthly payroll deductions to make covering the remaining cost easier.</quote>
    <link>https://news.aetna.com/news-releases/aetna-to-transform-members-consumer-health-experience-using-iphone-ipad-and-apple-watch/</link>
  </entry>
  
 
</feed>
