<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>September 25, 2015</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>For Preventing Disease, Data Are the New Drugs</title>
    <quote>A new cadre of medical researchers believes that examining the full genetic information of as many people as possible will reveal not just the cures for health problems ranging from pre-term birth to cancer and autism, but the predictive insight to prevent them from happening altogether.</quote>
    <link>http://nautil.us/issue/21/information/for-preventing-disease-data-are-the-new-drugs-rp</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Startup Shift Labs wants to change how medical devices are made</title>
    <quote>In 2011, Beth Kolko had an epiphany. At the time, she’d been working with a team of researchers on a project that delivered basic ultrasound technology to midwives in Uganda and Kenya. The idea, one of many she worked on as a professor at the Department of Human-Centered Design and Engineering at the University of Washington, was simple: create an easier way to monitor an individual’s health. </quote>
    <link>http://fortune.com/2015/09/09/shift-labs-medical-devices/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Product Design Workshop at HackMIT 2015</title>
    <quote>Don’t forget that people make the stuff. Relations make the bigger stuff. Get the relations and people part right, first. The rest will follow.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/@johnmaeda/product-design-workshop-at-hackmit-2015-596c94262147</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Can you “design” healthcare? It’s hard.</title>
    <quote>The next big frontier in healthcare lies in the hands of an unforeseen bunch. They’re not developing the next blockbuster drug or groundbreaking surgery. They’re not even publishing their celebrated research in medical journals. Designers are one of the most untapped, underutilized assets in the healthcare industry. Prescribe Design is about revealing healthcare’s new secret weapon: designers.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/tincture/designing-the-future-of-healthcare-510e98fd3aa7</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>THE DEFINITIVE iOS 9 review</title>
    <quote>After the radical redesign of iOS 7, which gave us a cleaner, more flexible experience, and the functional revolution of iOS 8, which extended and continued that experience between apps and devices, iOS 9 takes a moment to solidify and round-out everything that's come before, and start us towards everything that's coming next.</quote>
    <link>http://www.imore.com/ios-9-review</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
