<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>February 12, 2021</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The man who produced Steve Jobs’ keynotes for 20 years.</title>
    <quote>If you look at the primitive narratives in Steve’s presentations at NeXT, you can see the influence that our experience at Pixar had on the storytelling over time that resulted in events like the iPhone launch.</quote>
    <link>https://www.cake.co/conversations/jNZlq6j/the-man-who-produced-steve-jobs-keynotes-for-20-years</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Making Vaccine</title>
    <quote>Back in December, I asked how hard it would be to make a vaccine for oneself.</quote>
    <link>https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/niQ3heWwF6SydhS7R/making-vaccine</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Months after TikTok apologized to Black creators, many say little has changed</title>
    <quote>TikTok's popularity has been significantly helped by Black creatives, whose trends, dances and challenge ideas were often scooped up and repackaged by white creators, boosting those creators to internet stardom.</quote>
    <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/pop-culture-news/months-after-tiktok-apologized-black-creators-many-say-little-has-n1256726</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Africa's Hit Science Show For Kids Is Coming To The U.S.</title>
    <quote>Educators have praised the show for prominently featuring women. Christine Kathurima, principal of Nova Pioneer Schools, an independent school network spanning preschool to secondary grades in Kenya and South Africa, describes N*Gen as "absolutely ground-breaking in the quality and the African female presenters."</quote>
    <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2021/02/05/947587199/africas-hit-science-show-for-kids-is-coming-to-the-u-s</link>
  </entry>

   <entry>
    <title>The Doctor Will Sniff You Now</title>
    <quote>What can one’s odor tell about one’s health? Apparently, a lot. The information that can be picked up from the airborne molecules is amazingly rich</quote>
    <link>https://nautil.us/issue/95/escape/the-doctor-will-sniff-you-now</link>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
