<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>March 18, 2022</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Dual use of artificial-intelligence-powered drug discovery</title>
    <quote>An international security conference explored how artificial intelligence (AI) technologies for drug discovery could be misused for de novo design of biochemical weapons. A thought experiment evolved into a computational proof.</quote>
    <link>https://www.nature.com/articles/s42256-022-00465-9</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Deliberately Optimizing for Harm</title>
    <quote>The paper discusses ethics training, international agreements and guidelines, pledges of responsibility and so on. That's all fine, but history demonstrates that anyone truly interested in using such things will care nothing for these constraints.</quote>
    <link>https://www.science.org/content/blog-post/deliberately-optimizing-harm</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Re: Visualizing Black America</title>
    <quote>To celebrate Black History Month in February of 2022, the Baltimore Mayor’s Office of Performance and Innovation (OPI) teamed up with other City analysts to build a library of data visualizations inspired by W.E.B. Du Bois. Our goal was to learn from his team’s work, use modern data, and tell a present-day story about Blackness in America.</quote>
    <link>https://storymaps.arcgis.com/stories/6a3d50cf2db44fc6b6e0810a0040412a</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>NASA’s Webb Reaches Alignment Milestone, Optics Working Successfully</title>
    <quote>“We have fully aligned and focused the telescope on a star, and the performance is beating specifications. We are excited about what this means for science,” said Ritva Keski-Kuha, deputy optical telescope element manager for Webb at NASA Goddard. “We now know we have built the right telescope.”</quote>
    <link>https://www.nasa.gov/press-release/nasa-s-webb-reaches-alignment-milestone-optics-working-successfully</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2022 Data: Toxic Company Culture Is Fueling the Great Resignation</title>
    <quote>Among workers who quit during the Great Resignation, the most common reasons were toxic company culture (31%), poor company response to the COVID-19 pandemic (30%), and changing career goals (30%).</quote>
    <link>https://www.realestatewitch.com/great-resignation-2022/</link>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
