<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>August 12, 2016</date>
    
	<entry>
		<title>Gene-Therapy Cure Has Money-Back Guarantee</title>
		<quote>The most expensive drugs in history, or medicine’s biggest bargains? Gene therapy could be both.</quote>
		<link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/602113/gene-therapy-cure-has-money-back-guarantee/</link>
	</entry>
  
	<entry>
		<title>I Want to Know What Code Is Running Inside My Body</title>
		<quote>“I felt like I was going to die,” she says. “It was a horrible feeling. I had no breath left, I didn’t know what was happening.” Back in Norway, it took her cardiac technicians months to figure out what had happened: The heart rate limits on her pacemaker had been set incorrectly, so that as she exerted herself, the pacemaker’s default safety mode switched on, cutting her heart rate instantaneously from 160 beats per minute to 80.</quote>
		<link>https://backchannel.com/i-want-to-know-what-code-is-running-inside-my-body-ff9a159da34b#.jb2m3gwb7</link>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Beyond CRISPR: A guide to the many other ways to edit a genome</title>
		<quote>But for all the devotion, CRISPR–Cas9 has its limitations. It is excellent at going to a particular location on the genome and cutting there, says bioengineer Prashant Mali at the University of California, San Diego. “But sometimes your application of interest demands a bit more.”</quote>
		<link>http://www.nature.com/news/beyond-crispr-a-guide-to-the-many-other-ways-to-edit-a-genome-1.20388</link>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<title>The lost infrastructure of social media.</title>
		<quote>More than a decade ago, the earliest era of blogging provided a set of separate but related technologies that helped the nascent form thrive. Today, most have faded away and been forgotten, but new incarnations of these features could still be valuable.</quote>
		<link>https://medium.com/@anildash/the-lost-infrastructure-of-social-media-d2b95662ccd3#.cnvgkiw4n</link>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<title>Playing The Long Game Inside Tim Cook's Apple</title>
		<quote>What Apple has accomplished with Maps is an example of the kind of grind-it-out innovation that’s happening all the time at the company. You don’t hear a lot about it, perhaps because it doesn’t support the enthralling myth that innovation comes in blinding flashes that lead to hitherto unimaginable products. When critics ding Apple for its failure to introduce "breakthrough" devices and services, they are missing three key facts about technology: First, that breakthrough moments are unpredictable outcomes of ongoing, incremental innovation; second, that ongoing, behind-the-scenes innovation brings significant benefits, even if it fails to create singular disruptions; and, third, that new technologies only connect broadly when a mainstream audience is ready and has a compelling need. "The world thinks we delivered [a breakthrough] every year while Steve was here," says Cue. "Those products were developed over a long period of time."</quote>
		<link>http://www.fastcompany.com/3062090/tim-cooks-apple/playing-the-long-game-inside-tim-cooks-apple</link>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<title>What one assistant principal learned from shadowing a student for a day</title>
		<quote>High school students and parents sometimes say principals and teachers don’t quite understand what it’s like to be a student these days. It turns out there’s an effort to change that. Some 1,300 principals recently took a day off from their usual role and instead followed one of their students for a day. The approach came from two groups outside the traditional field of public education, the Design School at Stanford University, and IDEO, a design company based in Palo Alto, California.</quote>
		<link>http://www.pbs.org/newshour/bb/one-assistant-principal-learned-shadowing-student-day/</link>
	</entry>
</feed>
