<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>July 31, 2020</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Cold War Bunker That Became Home to a Dark-Web Empire</title>
    <quote>An eccentric Dutchman began living in a giant underground facility built by the German military—and ran a server farm beloved by cybercriminals.</quote>
    <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2020/08/03/the-cold-war-bunker-that-became-home-to-a-dark-web-empire</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>For Black entrepreneurs, the racial wealth gap makes finding funding nearly impossible</title>
    <quote>They need to understand that it’s about missed opportunity as well. Minorities as a consumer group represent nearly $4 trillion in buying power and significantly influence the mainstream. The fact of the matter is that investing in underrepresented communities is just smart and lucrative business.</quote>
    <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90531094/for-black-entrepreneurs-the-racial-wealth-gap-makes-finding-funding-nearly-impossible</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>We’re in a golden age of UX. Why is video chat still stuck in the ’90s?</title>
    <quote>In my line of work, we frequently host calls with a diverse set of participants, from large foundations, to governments, to community leaders. It’s about time we had a virtual environment that is conducive to these conversations.</quote>
    <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90529993/zoom-doesnt-need-to-be-so-awful-what-the-future-of-video-chat-could-learn-from-the-past</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Google’s Top Search Result?, Suprise! It's Google</title>
    <quote>We examined more than 15,000 recent popular queries and found that Google devoted 41 percent of the first page of search results on mobile devices to its own properties and what it calls “direct answers,” which are populated with information copied from other sources, sometimes without their knowledge or consent.</quote>
    <link>https://themarkup.org/google-the-giant/2020/07/28/google-search-results-prioritize-google-products-over-competitors</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Tech CEO Congressional Hearing: Recap of the biggest moments you missed</title>
    <quote>The hours-long hearing was marked by piercing questions about anti-competitive practices … as well as bizarre diversions into tech support and internet drama</quote>
    <link>https://www.digitaltrends.com/news/big-tech-congress-antitrust-hearing-live-news-google-apple-amazon-facebook/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>A Boy With Muscular Dystrophy Was Headed For A Wheelchair. Then Gene Therapy Arrived</title>
    <quote>This is the story of a fatal genetic disease, a tenacious scientist and a family that never lost hope.</quote>
    <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2020/07/27/893289171/a-boy-with-muscular-dystrophy-was-headed-for-a-wheelchair-then-gene-therapy-arri?t=1596017201435</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The End of Open-Plan Everything</title>
    <quote>Personal space is finally back in style, but re-creating it after two decades of its destruction is hardly a straightforward task.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2020/07/walls-pandemic-open-plan/614590/</link>
  </entry>

 


</feed>
