<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>June 25, 2021</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How a Sharp-Eyed Scientist Became Biology’s Image Detective</title>
    <quote>Using just her eyes and memory, Elisabeth Bik has single-handedly identified thousands of studies containing potentially doctored scientific images.</quote>
    <link>https://www.newyorker.com/science/elements/how-a-sharp-eyed-scientist-became-biologys-image-detective</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>NASA inches closer to printing artificial organs in space</title>
    <quote>Researchers used 3D-printing to create human liver tissue that could soon be tested on the International Space Station.</quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/06/18/1026556/nasa-bioprinting-artificial-organs-space/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>As The Pandemic Recedes, Millions Of Workers Are Saying 'I Quit'</title>
    <quote>As pandemic life recedes in the U.S., people are leaving their jobs in search of more money, more flexibility and more happiness. Many are rethinking what work means to them, how they are valued, and how they spend their time.</quote>
    <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/06/24/1007914455/as-the-pandemic-recedes-millions-of-workers-are-saying-i-quit</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Blood test that finds 50 types of cancer is accurate enough to be rolled out</title>
    <quote>Scientists said their findings, published in the journal Annals of Oncology, show that the test accurately detects cancer often before any signs or symptoms appear, while having a very low false positive rate.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2021/jun/25/blood-test-that-finds-50-types-of-cancer-is-accurate-enough-to-be-rolled-out</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Here are the visual changes Microsoft showed off in Windows 11</title>
    <quote>Microsoft announced Windows 11 today, and one of the headline features of the “next generation” operating system is its visual overhaul. It’s released an entire video about how it designed its new OS, which shows off the new rounded corners, icons, and more</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2021/6/24/22548895/windows-11-ui-visual-change-roundup-microsoft-upgrade</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
