<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>July 21, 2023</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Vera Molnár: The Grande Dame of Generative Art</title>
    <quote>nfluenced by her time among the post-WWII Paris avant-garde, Vera Molnár became one of the first artists to incorporate computers in her practice. Decades later, she’s still making radical works of digital art.</quote>
    <link>https://www.sothebys.com/en/articles/vera-molnar-the-grande-dame-of-generative-art</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>A 17th-century font in a 21st-century thesis</title>
    <quote>One day, I decided to visit my university library to see the original specimen sheet printed by William Caslon in 1741, in the library's rare book collection. It was a timeless experience seeing and handling the specimen sheet itself, not a digital scan of it. It was like a live performance of the Vienna Philharmonic at the Musikverein, versus an mp3 on the iPod.</quote>
    <link>https://www.linyangchen.com/Typography-Fell-Types-font</link>
  </entry>

    <entry>
    <title>TikTok is the most popular news source for 12 to 15-year-olds, says Ofcom</title>
    <quote>Algorithm-driven viral video app overtakes YouTube and Instagram as most used single source of news for young teenagers</quote>
    <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2023/jul/20/tiktok-is-the-most-popular-news-source-for-12-to-15-year-olds-says-ofcom</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Christopher Nolan wants Oppenheimer to be a cautionary tale for Silicon Valley </title>
    <quote>The film about a man who regrets his great technological innovation because he failed to consider its ramifications certainly does have some potential parallels.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2023/7/16/23796659/christopher-nolan-oppenheimer-ai-warning-silicon-valley</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Here’s why the best IMAX movies still need a Palm Pilot to work</title>
    <quote>Oppenheimer is 600 pounds of 70mm IMAX film, and it wouldn’t work so well on-screen if it weren’t for a 21-year-old PDA.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/23801118/imax-movie-palm-pilot-oppenheimer</link>
  </entry>
  



  
</feed>
