<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>April 15, 2022</date>

  <entry>
    <title>Google Search is Falling Behind</title>
    <quote>Three areas where Google Search lags behind its competitors: coding, cooking, and travel </quote>
    <link>https://www.surgehq.ai//blog/google-search-is-falling-behind</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Tech talent tectonics: Ten new realities for finding, keeping, and developing talent</title>
    <quote>In fact, developing robust people and talent strategies are among the highest-value actions a business can take. Tech talent, therefore, should be a CEO’s top priority. Based on our work on more than 80 technology-talent transformations, we have identified a set of ten realities companies need to face and what they can do to address them.</quote>
    <link>https://www.mckinsey.com/business-functions/mckinsey-digital/our-insights/tech-talent-tectonics-ten-new-realities-for-finding-keeping-and-developing-talent</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>It’s Still Stupidly, Ridiculously Difficult To Buy A ‘Dumb’ TV</title>
    <quote> Last year Vizio noted it made $38.4 million in one quarter just from tracking and monetizing consumer viewing and usage data. It made $48.2 million on hardware (which also includes soundbars, and other products) in that same period.</quote>
    <link>https://www.techdirt.com/2022/04/14/its-still-stupidly-ridiculously-difficult-to-buy-a-dumb-tv/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>The 8-year process behind Playdate’s glorious crank</title>
    <quote>From nearly day one, Panic’s portable console has been defined by a single feature hanging off its right side</quote>
    <link>https://www.polygon.com/23013686/playdate-panic-crank-history</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2022 10 Breakthrough Technologies</title>
    <quote>End Of Passwords, Covid Variant Tracking, A Long-lasting Grid Battery, Ai For Protein Folding, Malaria Vaccine, Proof Of Stake, A Pill For Covid, Practical Fusion Reactors, Synthetic Data For Ai, A Carbon Removal Factory, </quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/2022/02/23/1045416/10-breakthrough-technologies-2022</link>
  </entry>


  
</feed>
