<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>January 29, 2016</date>
  
 <entry>
    <title>Sharing Clinical Trial Data: A Proposal From the International Committee of Medical Journal Editors </title>
    <quote>The International Committee of Medical Journal Editors (ICMJE) believes that there is an ethical obligation to responsibly share data generated by interventional clinical trials because participants have put themselves at risk. In a growing consensus, many funders around the world—foundations, government agencies, and industry—now mandate data sharing. Here we outline ICMJE's proposed requirements to help meet this obligation. </quote>
    <link>http://annals.org/article.aspx?articleid=2482115</link>
  </entry>  

  <entry>
    <title>How Data Brokers Make Money Off Your Medical Records</title>
    <quote>Once upon a time, simply removing a person's name, address and Social Security number from a medical record may well have protected anonymity. Not so today. Straightforward data-mining tools can rummage through multiple databases containing anonymized and nonanonymized data to reidentify the individuals from their ostensibly private medical records.</quote>
    <link>http://www.scientificamerican.com/article/how-data-brokers-make-money-off-your-medical-records/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why Marketers Must Understand the Internet of Things</title>
    <quote>For marketers the IoT will have massive implications on how we develop and execute campaigns, structure our teams and optimize performance. We will shift our focus to gaining access to consumer and product IoT data at scale. We will be required to provide value to our key audiences in exchange for their permission to both capture their data and reach them directly. We will develop and optimize campaigns that use the data to trigger communications that compels action.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/@Edelman/why-marketers-must-understand-the-internet-of-things-b0f46ca771ca#.5go4grbom</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>The Surprising Benefits to Working with Long-distance Design Partners</title>
    <quote>Seeing how much design is influenced by a sense of place, space, and the immediate community, it makes sense that intense cross-country collaboration can only add something exciting to the visual vocabulary of design.</quote>
    <link>https://eyeondesign.aiga.org/the-surprising-benefits-to-working-with-long-distance-design-partners</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Enterprise Apps In The Field: How User Visits Become A Catalyst</title>
    <quote>They showed up in the field office to watch their users, the field representatives, do their jobs. Even though they’d been working on this project for a while — for some, it had been years — this was their first exposure to how the users did their work.
It was amazing to watch. They saw so many things different from what they expected.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/ux-immersion-interactions/enterprise-apps-in-the-field-how-user-visits-become-a-catalyst-1f2278581cb6#.md1kpx87i</link>
  </entry>
  
 
</feed>
