<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>April 30, 2021</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Breaking Camp</title>
    <quote>Basecamp announced it would ban “societal and political discussions” at work. But the hardest conversations at work were about the company itself.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2021/4/27/22406673/basecamp-political-speech-policy-controversy</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Facebook Stopped Employees From Reading An Internal Report About Its Role In The Insurrection. You Can Read It Here.</title>
    <quote>After BuzzFeed News reported on an internal document that examined the social network’s failings leading up to the Capitol riot, many of Facebook's employees were prevented from accessing it.</quote>
    <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/ryanmac/full-facebook-stop-the-steal-internal-report</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>TikTok and the Vibes Revival</title>
    <quote>Increasingly, what we’re after on social media is not narrative or personality but moments of audiovisual eloquence.</quote>
    <link>https://www.newyorker.com/culture/cultural-comment/tiktok-and-the-vibes-revival</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>'Full Of Hatred And Fear': Disinformation On YouTube Divided A Dad And Daughter</title>
    <quote>"The last time I saw my dad, he was painting my house," Ekwoge says. "He came and helped paint all weekend. It was nice when we lived closer and had ways to hang out that didn't include nonsense videos."</quote>
    <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/04/25/988860971/full-of-hatred-and-fear-disinformation-on-youtube-divided-a-dad-and-daughter</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Zoom’s Immersive View could make video calls feel a bit more in-person</title>
    <quote>Immersive View builds on the virtual background features Zoom already has, but focuses on actually placing meeting attendees in a realistic-looking location, rather than just switching out a flat background.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2021/4/26/22400362/zoom-immersive-view-meeting-virtual-backgrounds</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Just because you can work from home doesn’t mean you’ll be allowed to</title>
    <quote>Which jobs are heading back to the office and which can stay home varies widely.</quote>
    <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/22387529/working-from-home-return-to-office-remote-work</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
