<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>October 6, 2017</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Gene-Edited Skin Could Be Its Own Blood-Sugar Sensor</title>
    <quote>In a fascinating mashup of technologies, the Chicago team says it has genetically edited skin cells from a mouse and turned them into a glucose detector that, once grafted onto the animals, works all the time and doesn’t need a battery.
It’s the first time living skin has been turned into a sensor, says Wu, adding that “a skin-based technology would have a lot of advantages” over finger pricks or even the continuous monitors some diabetics use.</quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/609030/gene-edited-skin-could-be-its-own-blood-sugar-sensor/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>An open letter to Jeff Bezos–you are needed to disrupt the health care sector</title>
    <quote>Leave rationalizing the market for organic foods to one of your sidekicks, and tinkering with driverless cars to a crowded field of tech companies. You are needed to disrupt the health care sector. Only you have the vision, ambition, capital, and computing power this mission requires: Amazon Pharmacy, Amazon Analytic, Amazon Diagnostics</quote>
    <link>https://qz.com/1090762/an-open-letter-to-jeff-bezos-you-are-needed-to-disrupt-the-health-care-sector/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Sundar Pichai Says The Future Of Google Is Ai. But Can He Fix The Algorithm?</title>
    <quote>Most executives talk about AI like it's just another thing that's included in the box or in its cloud; it's a buzzword, a tick box on a spec sheet slotted in right after the processor. But Pichai is intent on pressing Google's advantage in AI — not just by integrating AI features into every product it makes, but by making products that are themselves inspired by AI, products that wouldn't be conceivable without it.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2017/10/4/16405174/ceo-sundar-pichai-interview-google-ai-artificial-intelligence-interface</link>
  </entry>


  <entry>
    <title>Forget Killer Robots—Bias Is the Real AI Danger</title>
    <quote>The problem of bias in machine learning is likely to become more significant as the technology spreads to critical areas like medicine and law, and as more people without a deep technical understanding are tasked with deploying it. Some experts warn that algorithmic bias is already pervasive in many industries, and that almost no one is making an effort to identify or correct it</quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/608986/forget-killer-robotsbias-is-the-real-ai-danger/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Stop doing user interviews. Start having conversations.</title>
    <quote>If you can level up by remembering your user interview skills and also relaxing and having a conversation, the person you’re talking to is going to be that much more engaged. If they’re engaged, what they tell you will be more natural, your insights will be deeper and learnings more nuanced. If they’re disengaged, you’ll get your yes, no answers, but they won’t feel like going deep, sharing their feelings, and opening up to you.</quote>
    <link>https://uxdesign.cc/stop-doing-user-interviews-start-having-conversations-187dc3328bf</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
</feed>
