<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>February 4, 2022</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Don’t forget Microsoft</title>
    <quote>Despite its scale, Microsoft is one of the most overlooked companies in tech. If it plays its cards right, Microsoft can become the first $10T company. And startup founders would be wise to learn from the behemoth in Redmond.</quote>
    <link>https://luttig.substack.com/p/dont-forget-microsoft</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why Facebook’s daily users are falling for the first time as Gen Z and millennials jump ship to TikTok</title>
    <quote>Meta’s share price dropped by around 20 per cent today as experts warned the platform faces a slow decline as it fails to attract younger users</quote>
    <link>https://inews.co.uk/news/technology/faceboo-daily-users-falling-gen-z-millenials-1440969</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>On Racialized Tech Organizations and Complaint: A Goodbye to Google</title>
    <quote>But Google’s toxic problems are no mystery to anyone who’s been there for more than a few months, or who have been following the tech news with a critical eye. </quote>
    <link>https://alex-hanna.medium.com/on-racialized-tech-organizations-and-complaint-a-goodbye-to-google-43fd8045991d</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Tech questions for 2022</title>
    <quote>Sometimes the centre of gravity in tech is very clear, but as we enter 2022 there are lots of areas where trillion dollar questions are wide open. These are the questions I wonder about today, from crypto to cars to fast fashion - there are others.</quote>
    <link>https://www.ben-evans.com/benedictevans/2022/1/2/2022-questions</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Andy Warhol, Clay Christensen, and Vitalik Buterin walk into a bar</title>
    <quote>The question of what makes things “valuable” in the first place is a wonderful lens through which to think about cryptocurrencies, NFTs, and meme stocks. As economist Mariana Mazzucato outlines in her book The Value of Everything, the notion of value is not fixed.</quote>
    <link>https://www.oreilly.com/radar/andy-warhol-clay-christensen-and-vitalik-buterin-walk-into-a-bar/</link>
  </entry>

  
  
</feed>
