<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>October 21, 2022</date>

  <entry>
    <title>Depending on where you live, the internet AT&amp;T offers you may be faster or slower.</title>
    <quote>The household with slower service is in a lower income area with fewer White residents...The slower service does not come with a better price. Both households are asked to pay exactly the same.</quote>
    <link>https://themarkup.org/still-loading/2022/10/19/dollars-to-megabits-you-may-be-paying-400-times-as-much-as-your-neighbor-for-internet-service</link>
  </entry>
  

  <entry>
    <title>Playing Dataviz Tennis for Collaboration and Fun</title>
    <quote>Inspired by Layer Tennis, we collaborated on four data visualizations (four matches) where we swap the file back and forth adding to the work. Each match lasted for eight or 10 rounds with 45 minutes per round, and the person who served got to choose the dataset for the match.</quote>
    <link>https://nightingaledvs.com/playing-dataviz-tennis-for-collaboration-and-fun/</link>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>How many Amazon packages get delivered each year?</title>
    <quote>In 2021 the company shipped an estimated 7.7 billion packages globally, based on its nearly $470 billion in sales.</quote>
    <link>https://theconversation.com/how-many-amazon-packages-get-delivered-each-year-187587?</link>
  </entry>

<entry>
    <title>Rent Going Up? One Company’s Algorithm Could Be Why.</title>
    <quote>Texas-based RealPage’s YieldStar software helps landlords set prices for apartments across the U.S. With rents soaring, critics are concerned that the company’s proprietary algorithm is hurting competition.</quote>
    <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/yieldstar-rent-increase-realpage-rent</link>
  </entry>  
  <entry>
    <title>How to organize your Slack channels </title>
    <quote>Conversations in Slack can quickly get out of hand — so it’s a good idea to try to organize them to help keep track</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/23411393/slack-channels-organize-how-to</link>
  </entry>


</feed>
