<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>February 5, 2016</date>
  
   <entry>
    <title>Open source lessons for synthetic biology</title>
    <quote>Can a larger firm thus make money from open source biology? We believe so, provided the company uses a method similar to Red Hat, Google, or Tesla, in using the open source component to drive customers toward their own market strength</quote>
    <link>http://radar.oreilly.com/2015/10/open-source-lessons-for-synthetic-biology.html</link>
  </entry> 
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Complexity of Simple</title>
    <quote>Given all the various options, what will we ship as the default?” Then, I like to say, “That’s our product.” How often do regular people dig around in the settings? People generally just want products that work well.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/the-biz-stone-collection/the-complexity-of-simple-a2d4dd38bf3#.rwfwxs8ji</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Make journals report clinical trials properly</title>
    <quote>Our group has taken a new approach to trying to fix this problem. Since last October, we have been checking the outcomes reported in every trial published in five top medical journals against the pre-specified outcomes from the registry entries or protocols. Most had discrepancies, many of them major. Then, crucially, we have submitted a correction letter, on every trial that misreported its outcomes, to the journal in question.</quote>
    <link>http://www.nature.com/news/make-journals-report-clinical-trials-properly-1.19280</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>AI Is Transforming Google Search. The Rest of the Web Is Next</title>
    <quote>Artificial intelligence is the future of Google Search, and if it’s the future of Google Search, it’s the future of so much more.</quote>
    <link>http://www.wired.com/2016/02/ai-is-changing-the-technology-behind-google-searches/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>My Bathroom Mirror Is Smarter Than Yours</title>
    <quote>Sometime late last year I realized that I wanted my ordinary bathroom mirror to be more like the future we were promised in the movies.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/@maxbraun/my-bathroom-mirror-is-smarter-than-yours-94b21c6671ba#.bn1khmk11</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
</feed>
