<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>August 2, 2019</date> 
  
  <entry>
    <title>Fast Software, the Best Software</title>
    <quote>I love fast software. That is, software speedy both in function and interface. Software with minimal to no lag between wanting to activate or manipulate something and the thing happening. Lightness.</quote>
    <link>https://craigmod.com/essays/fast_software/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How Phones Made the World Your Office, Like It or Not</title>
    <quote>The telephone began to pervade our lives at the end of the 19th century, and then — as you can see in these photos from The New York Times’s archives — it became our lives. Cellphones were a significant inflection point. They made it possible for us to be available at virtually any moment, which was so extraordinary that most of us tacitly accepted that we should be available at virtually any moment.</quote>
    <link>https://nyti.ms/2YyUfzB</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Machine Learning That’s Light Enough for an Arduino</title>
    <quote>I want to find out what happens when we bring machine learning to cheap, robust devices that can have all kinds of sensors and work in all kinds of environments. And I want you to help. The kind of AI we can squeeze into a US $30 or $40 system won’t beat anyone at Go, but it opens the door to applications we might never even imagine otherwise.</quote>
    <link>https://spectrum.ieee.org/geek-life/hands-on/machine-learning-thats-light-enough-for-an-arduino</link>
  </entry>
  
 <entry>
    <title>London Lab Advances Use of A.I. in Health Care, but Raises Privacy Concerns</title>
    <quote>In a paper published on Wednesday in the science journal Nature, researchers from DeepMind, a London artificial intelligence lab owned by Google’s parent company, detail a system that can analyze a patient’s health records, including blood tests, vital signs and past medical history, and predict A.K.I. up to 48 hours before onset.</quote>
    <link>https://nyti.ms/2KhcW1A</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Would You Want a Computer to Judge Your Risk of H.I.V. Infection?</title>
    <quote>A new software algorithm decides which patients are most likely to become infected with the virus. Does the assessment stigmatize patients?</quote>
    <link>https://nyti.ms/2YrjdwD</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
