<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>December 10, 2021</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Over 40 million people had health information leaked this year</title>
    <quote>Over 40 million people in the United States had their personal health information exposed in data breaches this year, a significant jump from 2020 and a continuation of a trend toward more and more health data hacks and leaks.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2021/12/8/22822202/health-data-leaks-hacks?scrolla=5eb6d68b7fedc32c19ef33b4</link>
  </entry>

   <entry>
    <title>Three Steps to the Future</title>
    <quote>The most exciting themes in technology today are transformative visions for 2025 or 2030: crypto, web3, VR, metaverse… and then everything else. Meanwhile, hundreds of start-ups take ideas from the last decade and deploy them over and over in one industry after another. And trying to keep up, the old economy faces waves of disruption from ideas we first talked about in the 1990s.</quote>
    <link>https://www.ben-evans.com/presentations</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>52 things I learned in 2021</title>
    <quote>...Early versions of PowerPoint were created by a technical team that was 43% women, compared to an average of 10% in Silicon Valley at the time. </quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/fluxx-studio-notes/52-things-i-learned-in-2021-8481c4e0d409</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>What Google’s trending searches say about America in 2021</title>
    <quote>Wolf haircuts and Wall Street: What Americans googled this year.</quote>
    <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/22822257/google-trending-searches-2021-america</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How Louis Armstrong Shaped the Sound of Ghana</title>
    <quote>Today, Ghana is a thriving country with a stable democracy and its own distinctive beat—highlife. The homegrown musical genre, a blend of local indigenous melodies and rhythms with elements of jazz, all played on Western instruments, became a voice of the emerging nation thanks in large part to Armstrong’s visit, and it is now experiencing a resurgence within the country, as Ghana reexamines the legacy of the slave trade and the African diaspora</quote>
    <link>https://www.atlasobscura.com/articles/louis-armstrong-jazz-highlife-ghana</link>
  </entry>

 
  
</feed>
