<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>October 6, 2023</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Shift Happens is a beautifully designed history of how keyboards got this way</title>
    <quote>Marcin Wichary on his long quest to capture everything that shaped modern type.</quote>
    <link>https://arstechnica.com/culture/2023/10/shift-happens-is-a-beautifully-designed-history-of-how-keyboards-got-this-way</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Ring Is Cashing In on the UFO Craze to Promote Its Surveillance Dystopia</title>
    <quote>The 'Million Dollar Sighting' contest will reward people for putting up cameras in their home and capturing irrefutable proof of extraterrestrials.</quote>
    <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/g5y8m3/ring-is-cashing-in-on-the-ufo-craze-to-promote-its-surveillance-dystopia</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Nobel Prize in medicine won by two scientists for ‘groundbreaking findings’ on mRNA Covid-19 vaccines</title>
    <quote>Karikó and Weissman published their results in a 2005 paper that received little attention at the time, it said, but later laid the foundation for critically important developments that served humanity during the coronavirus pandemic.</quote>
    <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2023/10/02/europe/nobel-prize-medicine-mrna-covid-vaccines-2023-intl-scn/index.html</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Authors shocked to find AI ripoffs of their books being sold on Amazon</title>
    <quote>But glancing at a few passages revealed that Cellan-Jones had fallen victim to someone attempting to piggyback on his memoir by releasing a title with text apparently generated by artificial intelligence – one of an influx of AI titles since the emergence of ChatGPT enabled people to generate pages of text rather than bothering to write it.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2023/sep/30/authors-shocked-to-find-ai-ripoffs-of-their-books-being-sold-on-amazon</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Why Timnit Gebru wants AI giants to think small</title>
    <quote>When a select few companies in Silicon Valley promise more than their technology can actually deliver, Gebru argues, it makes it even harder for smaller companies to compete.</quote>
    <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90952740/why-timnit-gebru-wants-ai-giants-to-think-small</link>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
