<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>February 10, 2017</date>
  
  <entry>
  	<title>Doctors See Gains Against ‘an Urgent Threat,’ C. Diff</title>
  	<quote>Though C. diff, as the bug is known, was identified in the 1930s, it became one of the country’s prime health concerns only a few years ago, after a particularly virulent and drug-resistant strain called NAP1 emerged in the 2000s....Vaccines may eventually prevent C. diff infection. Last year, the pharmaceutical company Sanofi began recruiting 15,000 volunteers for a Phase 3 trial of an experimental vaccine in about 20 countries. Pfizer and the French firm Valneva have also completed Phase 2 studies of possible vaccines.</quote>
  	<link>https://nyti.ms/2ktGXgA</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Watch: The paper-airplane drones that may one day save your life</title>
    <quote>DARPA, the United States military’s experimental technology arm, awarded a grant to the aerodynamics research group at Otherlab in San Francisco to develop a disposable glider that can be used to ferry medical supplies or other cargo to places where delivery people can’t go. This is particularly useful in situations where there’s been a disease outbreak and vaccines are urgently needed — or in areas where the road or terrain conditions are so treacherous that it would take far too long for a ground vehicle to make the trek.</quote>
    <link>http://www.recode.net/2017/1/31/14460734/watch-paper-airplane-drones-darpa-medicine</link>
  </entry>
  
 <entry>
    <title>The year in new drugs</title>
    <quote>After two years of an open spigot, the flow of new drugs tapered off in 2016. Just 22 new molecular entities were approved in the U.S. last year—less than half the number given the green light in 2015. Industry watchers are left puzzling over how to interpret the drop: as a bad omen for innovation or simply a blip in an otherwise upward trend in productivity?</quote>
    <link>http://cen.acs.org/articles/95/i5/year-new-drugs.html</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Inside Dropbox’s Identity Overhaul</title>
    <quote>Put it all together and you have, Houston says, a unique effort to unite the two realms of computing between which we hop back and forth today: “File world,” the drives and directories where our work products and documents live, and “cloud world,” the networked environment where we communicate and collaborate.</quote>
    <link>https://backchannel.com/inside-dropboxs-identity-overhaul-3104d184a1f7#.msb371pht</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Socially Sensitive AI Software Coaches Call-Center Workers</title>
    <quote>Some call-center workers are now receiving real-time coaching from software that analyzes their speech and the nature of their dialogue interactions with customers. As they are talking to someone the software might recommend that they talk more slowly or interrupt less often, or warn that the person on the other end of the line seems upset.</quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/603529/socially-sensitive-ai-software-coaches-call-center-workers</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
