<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>January 26, 2018</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Apple, in Sign of Health Ambitions, Adds Medical Records Feature for iPhone</title>
    <quote>The feature is to become part of Apple’s popular Health app. It will enable users to transfer clinical data — like cholesterol levels and lists of medications prescribed by their doctors — directly from their medical providers to their iPhones, potentially streamlining how Americans gain access to some health information.</quote>
    <link>https://nyti.ms/2F7zkX8</link>
  </entry>
  

  <entry>
    <title>Fed Up With Drug Companies, Hospitals Decide to Start Their Own</title>
    <quote>For years, hospital executives have expressed frustration when essential drugs like heart medicines have become scarce, or when prices have skyrocketed because investors manipulated the market.

Now, some of the country’s largest hospital systems are taking an aggressive step to combat the problem: They plan to go into the drug business themselves, in a move that appears to be the first on this scale.</quote>
    <link>https://nyti.ms/2Dg6nYy</link>
  </entry>


  <entry>
    <title>Amazon Go And The Future</title>
    <quote>The economics of Amazon Go define the tech industry; the strategy, though, is uniquely Amazon’s. Most of all, the implications of Amazon Go explain both the challenges and opportunities faced by society broadly by the rise of tech.</quote>
    <link>https://stratechery.com/2018/amazons-go-and-the-future/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The UX of AI</title>
    <quote>Using Google Clips to understand how a human-centered design process elevates artificial intelligence</quote>
    <link>https://design.google/library/ux-ai/</link>
  </entry>
  
    <entry>
    <title>Google’s self-training AI turns coders into machine-learning masters</title>
    <quote>A new service, called Cloud AutoML, uses several machine-learning tricks to automatically build and train a deep-learning algorithm that can recognize things in images.</quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/609996/googles-self-training-ai-turns-coders-into-machine-learning-masters/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
</feed>
