<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>September 22, 2023</date>
  <entry>
    <title>Google’s Bard chatbot can now find answers in your Gmail, Docs, Drive</title>
    <quote>Google’s Bard AI chatbot is no longer limited to pulling answers from just the web — it can now scan your Gmail, Docs, and Drive to help you find the information you’re looking for</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/19/23878999/google-bard-ai-chatbot-gmail-docs-drive-extensions</link>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Why Oppenheimer’s Cinematography is so Special</title>
    <quote>Not many movies these days are shot on the "old" analog film format because of the rise of digital cameras, however Christopher Nolan and Quentin are filmmakers who swear by analog film. Why is it that? Is it pure nostalgia? Does that mean analog is still better than digital? Or is there something bigger underlying their choice? Let's find out...</quote>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bixk5IH82h4</link>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Computing History Hub</title>
    <quote>Hi! This is a resource for learning about the history of computing, the design of user interfaces, and why we interact with these machines the way that we do. Each database includes a Start here view — consider these hand-picked as first reads.</quote>
    <link>https://mollymielke.notion.site/Computing-History-Hub-be72f307fc2e4b05abe3dc67eb937521</link>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>XML is better than YAML. Hear me out...</title>
    <quote>My spicy take is that XML is better than YAML, because there are situations where XML is appropriate, but there’s no situation where YAML is appropriate.</quote>
    <link>https://changelog.com/posts/xml-better-than-yaml</link>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Study Finds 95 Percent Of NFTs Are Now Worthless</title>
    <quote>"This daunting reality should serve as a sobering check on the euphoria that has often surrounded the NFT space," dappGambl's analysis reads. "Amid stories of digital art pieces selling for millions and overnight success stories, it is easy to overlook the fact that the market is fraught with pitfalls and potential losses."</quote>
    <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/study-nfts-worthless</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
