<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>September 24, 2021</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>This 3D Map of the Undersea Cables Connecting the Globe is Mesmerizing</title>
    <quote>A world of information is thrumming through miles of cables laying on the ocean floor. This map will show you where they are.</quote>
    <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/akgbea/this-3d-map-of-the-undersea-cables-connecting-the-globe-is-mesmerizing</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Black Girls Code's Founder on the Power of Trusting Your Intuition</title>
    <quote>Kimberly Bryant says listening to her gut, despite what others advised her, was one of the best moves she ever made for her company.</quote>
    <link>https://www.inc.com/anna-meyer/black-girls-code-kimberly-bryant-your-next-move.html</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>FILE NOT FOUND</title>
    <quote>A generation that grew up with Google is forcing professors to rethink their lesson plans</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/22684730/students-file-folder-directory-structure-education-gen-z</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The bias that blinds: why some people get dangerously different medical care</title>
    <quote>Medical research and practice have long assumed a narrow definition of the ‘default’ human, badly compromising the care of anyone outside that category. How can this be fixed?</quote>
    <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/sep/21/bias-that-blinds-medical-research-treatment-race-gender-dangerous-disparity</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>“Completely Running Blind.” Apple’s Power Move To Kneecap Facebook Advertising Is Working.</title>
    <quote>People are opting out of Facebook’s tracking for a reason: they no longer trust the company with their data after years of evidence they should not. But the context of Apple’s power move is important too. The company competes with Facebook’s messaging apps, and it’s working hard to build a robust ad platform of its own.</quote>
    <link>https://bigtechnology.substack.com/p/completely-running-blind-apples-power</link>
  </entry>
  
</feed>

