<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>November 19, 2021</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Do-It-Yourself artificial pancreas given approval by team of experts</title>
    <quote>More than 40 healthcare professionals and legal experts have issued the first guidance of its kind to support people with type 1 diabetes using Do-it-Yourself (DIY) technology driven systems to manage their condition.</quote>
    <link>https://www.kcl.ac.uk/news/do-it-yourself-artificial-pancreas-given-approval-by-team-of-experts</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Animation: How mRNA vaccines work</title>
    <quote>COVID-19 mRNA vaccines deliver directions to make a protein that educates our immune system, so it will neutralize the virus in future encounters.</quote>
    <link>https://youtu.be/8nD6Q9X0SFw</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Arthur C Clarke predicts the internet in 1964</title>
    <quote>These things will make possuble a world in which we can be in instant contact with each other where ever we may be; where we can contact our friends anywhere on earth if we don;t know their actual physical location. It will be possible for a man to conduct is business from Haiti or Bali just as well as he could from London.  Any skill could be made independent of distance.</quote>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wC3E2qTCIY8</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why NFTs are bad: the long version</title>
    <quote>NFTs (non-fungible tokens) are intended to be unique digital identifiers; a kind of “uncompromisable digital record”. They are not in fact anything like this, but this is what they claim to be.</quote>
    <link>https://antsstyle.medium.com/why-nfts-are-bad-the-long-version-2c16dae145e2</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Apple's Lost Future: Phone, Tablet, And Laptop Prototypes Of The ’80s</title>
    <quote>Some of the mockups still look sleek and stylish today, but few resemble the reality of the tablets, laptops, and phones that Apple would actually come to make two decades later, after Jobs' return.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2014/5/28/5757414/apple-prototype-tablets-phones-laptops-from-the-80s-photos</link>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
