<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>November 15, 2019</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Behind the Scenes of a Radical New Cancer Cure</title>
    <quote>What if we could go one step further? What if we could genetically engineer a patient’s own immune cells to spot and fight cancer, as a sort of “best hits” of genetic therapy and immunotherapy?</quote>
    <link>https://blogs.scientificamerican.com/observations/behind-the-scenes-of-a-radical-new-cancer-cure/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Apple just released an app that tracks your heart, hearing, and menstrual cycles</title>
    <quote>the app is meant to collect user data and send it to research partnerships that Apple has set up—three of them, each of which will focus on a separate issue. The first, on women’s health, links the company with Harvard’s public health school and the National Institutes of Health. The second study focuses on noise pollution and headphone usage, sharing data with the University of Michigan and the World Health Organization. The last is on heart and movement, with researchers from Brigham and Women’s Hospital and the American Heart Association.</quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/f/614717/apple-just-released-an-app-research-that-tracks-your-heart-hearing-and-menstrual-cycles/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Does AI Have a Place in Medicine?</title>
    <quote>Currently, our team is using AI to find the hidden pearls of wisdom buried inside massive reams of data. At the same time, we are striving to create a new, hybrid role—what we call “physician data scientists”—who understand machine learning, AI and how these technologies can be applied to medical research and clinical practice. Our goal is to improve patient outcomes and drive down costs.</quote>
    <link>https://blogs.scientificamerican.com/observations/does-ai-have-a-place-in-medicine/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Greatest Library You’ve Never Heard Of: ‘The Visual Telling Of Stories’</title>
    <quote>Dr. Chris Mullen’s drive to collect and share information has created a fascinating archive with a focus on Fortunes Magazine and the history of visual communication</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/nightingale/the-greatest-library-youve-never-heard-of-the-visual-telling-of-stories-9c6e67437483</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How the Dumb Design of a WWII Plane Led to the Macintosh</title>
    <quote>But Chapanis and Fitts were proposing something deeper than a solution for airplane crashes. Faced with the prospect of soldiers losing their lives to poorly designed machinery, they invented a new paradigm for viewing human behavior. That paradigm lies behind the user-friendly world that we live in every day. They realized that it was absurd to train people to operate a machine and assume they would act perfectly under perfect conditions.</quote>
    <link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-dumb-design-wwii-plane-led-macintosh/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
</feed>
