<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>January 22, 2021</date>

  <entry>
    <title>Capitol Attack Was Months in the Making on Facebook</title>
    <quote>Facebook spent the past year allowing election conspiracies and far-right militia activity to proliferate on its platform, laying the groundwork for the broader radicalization that fueled the Capitol insurrection in the first place.</quote>
    <link>https://www.techtransparencyproject.org/articles/capitol-attack-was-months-making-facebook</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Intel Problems</title>
    <quote>What is more concerning is that the question is no longer about seizing an opportunity but about survival, and it is the United States that has the most to lose.</quote>
    <link>https://stratechery.com/2021/intel-problems/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Exploring the Supply Chain of the Pfizer/BioNTech and Moderna COVID-19 vaccines</title>
    <quote>The following text is a collection of notes I wrote down while exploring the process for manufacturing and distributing the two new vaccines that have appeared all over the news and in more and more people’s arms over the recent weeks. I started reading about mRNA but quickly found myself on tangents about glass vials and temperature tracking devices.</quote>
    <link>https://blog.jonasneubert.com/2021/01/10/exploring-the-supply-chain-of-the-pfizer-biontech-and-moderna-covid-19-vaccines/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Cancer can be precisely diagnosed using a urine test with artificial intelligence</title>
    <quote>As a noninvasive method, a diagnostic test using urine is convenient for patients and does not need invasive biopsy, thereby diagnosing cancer without side effects.</quote>
    <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-01-cancer-precisely-urine-artificial-intelligence.html</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Google threatens to remove its search engine from Australia if new law goes into effect</title>
    <quote>Google is threatening to pull its search engine from an entire country — Australia — if a proposed law goes into effect that would force Google to pay news publishers for their content.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2021/1/21/22243468/google-threatens-to-remove-its-search-engine-from-australia-if-new-law-goes-into-effect</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Have We Already Been Visited by Aliens?</title>
    <quote>An eminent astrophysicist argues that signs of intelligent extraterrestrial life have appeared in our skies. What’s the evidence for his extraordinary claim?</quote>
    <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/01/25/have-we-already-been-visited-by-aliens</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Star Wars PDP-11/45</title>
    <quote>Restoring the original computer used to produce the grapics for Star Wars</quote>
    <link>https://toobnix.org/videos/watch/1c110cea-7605-4411-8415-23c35c6c4edf</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Why webcams aren't good enough</title>
    <quote>After consulting numerous webcam buying guides and reviews, purchasing a handful of the most popular models, and testing them in varying lighting situations, I can't escape the grim truth: there are no good webcams. Even webcams recommended by reputable outlets produce poor quality imagery—a significant failing, given it’s the one job they're supposed to provide.</quote>
    <link>https://reincubate.com/support/how-to/why-are-webcams-bad/#putting-them-to-the-test</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
