<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>October 29, 2021</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Apple’s Long Journey to the M1 Pro Chip</title>
    <quote>When you look at M1 Pro/Max today it is tempting to think of this in terms of performance, but performance per watt AND integrated graphics AND integrated memory AND integrated application processors is innovation in an entirely different direction. Just the beginning.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.learningbyshipping.com/apples-long-journey-to-the-m1-pro-chip-250309905358</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Inside the Facebook Papers</title>
    <quote>A WIRED series dives into thousands of internal documents, showing a company rife with issues that it largely failed to address.</quote>
    <link>https://www.wired.com/story/facebook-papers-internal-documents/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>New computer modelling could boost drug discovery</title>
    <quote>The computer modeling tool will predict novel sites of binding for potential drugs that are more selective, leading to more effective drug targeting, increasing therapeutic efficacy and reducing side effects.</quote>
    <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-10-boost-drug-discovery.html</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Jobs that Marry Together the Most</title>
    <quote>In the chart below, based on estimates from the American Community Survey, find out which jobs most often pair together among married couples.</quote>
    <link>https://flowingdata.com/2021/05/26/jobs-that-marry-together/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>The Traitorous Eight and the Battle of Germanium Valley</title>
    <quote>But even without the racism and paranoia, Shockley was a genuinely terrible manager. He was prone to starting and then halting projects, switching up the corporate priorities based on his whims without regard to the work that his employees had put into work that he was scrapping or de-emphasizing.
Within a year of the company’s founding, eight of its top engineers had had enough. They quit Shockley Semi and founded their own rival, Fairchild Semiconductor. Less than a year after that, Fairchild launched its first silicon transistor,</quote>
    <link>https://onezero.medium.com/a-the-traitorous-eight-and-the-battle-of-germanium-valley-86c455967d43</link>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
