<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>April 1, 2016</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Mapping a Genetic Strategy to Fight the Zika Virus</title>
    <quote>But the story of how the Aedes Genome Working Group emerged offers a glimpse at the often ad hoc way science lurches forward, driven by self-interest, new technology and pressing social needs. The pursuits of its members reflect the range of hopes for a new form of genetic combat that may be increasingly called into play as the specter of diseases borne by insects grows along with our ability to parse the details of their DNA.</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/2315wBX</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Let Patients Read Their Medical Records</title>
    <quote>A quarter of patients remain unaware of their right to an electronic copy of their medical records. But patients who frequently access their medical records may be more motivated to take control of their health — and in a better position to correct outdated or erroneous information.</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/234VTCq</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why Apple and Google are struggling to design simple software</title>
    <quote>That's not a function of slowing innovation or technological progress -- these features have been developed and shipped in finished products. If most people still don't understand how to use them? That's a design problem.</quote>
    <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/the-switch/wp/2016/03/28/why-apple-and-google-are-struggling-to-design-simple-software</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Unintuitive Lessons on Being a Designer</title>
    <quote>The either-or trap is completely false. A design can be easy to understand AND feel exceptionally well-crafted. It’s entirely possible to do good work across multiple dimensions. That should be the bar we aim for.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/the-year-of-the-looking-glass/8-unintuitive-lessons-on-being-a-designer-ca7e97a572ee#.trvdl2ab3</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
</feed>
