<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>May 22, 2015</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How a Childhood Vaccine Reduces Risk of a Cancer</title>
    <quote>Dr. Müschen, a professor of medicine at the University of California, San Francisco, said that the effect of the vaccine was a 20 percent reduction in risk for leukemia. “This seems small,” he said. “But it’s highly significant in large populations.</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/1efHiQh</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Top 10 data mining algorithms in plain English</title>
    <quote>Today, I’m going to explain in plain English the top 10 most influential data mining algorithms as voted on by 3 separate panels. Once you know what they are, how they work, what they do and where you can find them, my hope is you’ll have this blog post as a springboard to learn even more about data mining.</quote>
    <link>http://rayli.net/blog/data/top-10-data-mining-algorithms-in-plain-english/</link>
    <link>http://www.cs.uvm.edu/~icdm/algorithms/10Algorithms-08.pdf</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Apple Watch And Continuous Computing</title>
    <quote>But any interaction with your phone is still a cloistered one — you, your phone, and nothing else — which to my mind leaves at least one more evolutionary jump: continuous computing, no matter your context. Indeed, when it comes to ensuring a computer is always present and always accessible, the wrist is both natural and interesting.</quote>
    <link>https://stratechery.com/2015/apple-watch-and-continuous-computing/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Dieter Rams and the Relevance of Functionalism</title>
    <quote>From the creation of his first product in 1955 for Braun, Dieter Rams, one of the most popular industrial designers, has lead and laid guidelines for the Functionalist design movement. Functionalist design is a design movement in which the form of the object is driven by the purpose of the object and not by its aesthetics.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/@amarchadgar/dieter-rams-and-the-relevance-of-functionalism-65bf7c1af064</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
</feed>
