<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>September 23, 2022</date>


<entry>
    <title>How “Spider-Verse” forced animation to evolve</title>
    <quote>And while studios and independent artists tested out more stylized approaches in short films, no studio would commit to a feature-length animated movie that looked too different...That is, until Sony Pictures/Imageworks took on Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse. Instead of chasing the look everyone else was after, the team wanted to create something visually new. They did it with non-photorealistic rendering.</quote>
    <link>https://www.vox.com/videos/23349660/spider-verse-cgi-animation-pixar-photorealism</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>New Webb Image Captures Clearest View of Neptune’s Rings in Decades</title>
    <quote>NASA’s James Webb Space Telescope shows off its capabilities closer to home with its first image of Neptune. Not only has Webb captured the clearest view of this distant planet’s rings in more than 30 years, but its cameras reveal the ice giant in a whole new light.</quote>
    <link>https://www.nasa.gov/feature/goddard/2022/new-webb-image-captures-clearest-view-of-neptune-s-rings-in-decades</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>We’ve only just begun to examine the racial disparities of long covid</title>
    <quote>It may take years to understand the full impact of the pandemic and its aftermath on Black people in the US.</quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/2022/09/20/1059679/racial-disparities-of-long-covid/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>I tried replacing Google with TikTok, and it worked better than I thought</title>
    <quote>Prabhakar Raghavan, the SVP of search at Google, said in July that “something like almost 40 percent of young people, when they are looking for a place for lunch, they don’t go to Google Maps or Search, they go to TikTok or Instagram.”</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/23365101/tiktok-search-google-replacement</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>A history of ARM, part 1: Building the first chip</title>
    <quote>“We thought we were crazy," she said. "We thought we wouldn't be able to do it. But we kept finding that there was no actual stopping place. It was just a matter of doing the work.”</quote>
    <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2022/09/a-history-of-arm-part-1-building-the-first-chip/</link>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
