<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>February 26, 2016</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>A Do-It-Yourself Revolution in Diabetes Care</title>
    <quote>“Once I got all the pieces together, I remember crying — not quite in sadness, just in utter amazement — the first time I could see her numbers displayed on my computer screen and she was on the other side of the house”</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/1RisGyh</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Break Up the Insulin Racket</title>
    <quote>Insulin has been around for almost a century. The World Health Organization considers it an essential medicine, which means it should be available “at a price the individual and the community can afford.” So why is this product increasingly too expensive for many Americans?</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/1oB2WnB</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What’s Next in Computing?</title>
    <quote>The product cycle by comparison gets relatively little attention, even though it is what actually drives the computing industry forward. We can try to understand and predict the product cycle by studying the past and extrapolating into the future.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/@cdixon/what-s-next-in-computing-e54b870b80cc#.kfrsrasxe</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What Google Learned From Its Quest to Build the Perfect Team</title>
    <quote> As the researchers studied the groups, however, they noticed two behaviors that all the good teams generally shared. First, on the good teams, members spoke in roughly the same proportion […] Second, the good teams all had high ‘‘average social sensitivity’’ — a fancy way of saying they were skilled at intuiting how others felt based on their tone of voice, their expressions, and other nonverbal cues.</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/20Vn3sz</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Data-informed Design in practice</title>
    <quote>DDD is a systematic approach to the development and evolution of digital (and not only) services. As data becomes more accessible, decisions for design can be based on that data. To put it more simply; data complements design.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/interactive-mind/data-informed-design-in-practice-6eae192f11f0#.59oelr6yx</link>
  </entry>

</feed>
