<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>January 15, 2021</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What’s Wrong with the Way We Work</title>
    <quote>Americans are told to give their all—time, labor, and passion—to their jobs. But do their jobs give enough back?</quote>
    <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/01/18/whats-wrong-with-the-way-we-work</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Parler Users Breached Deep Inside U.S. Capitol Building, GPS Data Shows</title>
    <quote>The data, obtained by a computer hacker through legal means ahead of Parler’s shutdown on Monday, offers a bird’s eye view of its users swarming the Capitol grounds after receiving encouragement from President Trump — and during a violent breach that sent lawmakers and Capitol Hill visitors scrambling amid gunshots and calls for their death.</quote>
    <link>https://gizmodo.com/parler-users-breached-deep-inside-u-s-capitol-building-1846042905</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>70TB of Parler users’ messages, videos, and posts leaked by security researchers</title>
    <quote>However, after the news about the data scrape went global, the author of the hack @donk_enby explained in a tweet that neither her nor others have collected any personal data that Parler users did not make public themselves.</quote>
    <link>https://cybernews.com/news/70tb-of-parler-users-messages-videos-and-posts-leaked-by-security-researchers/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Internet 3.0 and the Beginning of (Tech) History</title>
    <quote>It turns out that when it comes to Information Technology, very little is settled; after decades of developing the Internet and realizing its economic potential, the entire world is waking up to the reality that the Internet is not simply a new medium, but a new maker of reality.</quote>
    <link>https://stratechery.com/2021/internet-3-0-and-the-beginning-of-tech-history/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The paradox of online “body positivity”</title>
    <quote> NBC News spoke to seven women in their teens and 20s who said that the content they viewed on the app had “pushed them to fixate more on their diets and exercise regimens to a dangerous extent.” Sissy Sheridan, a 16-year-old actress and social media star who is often cited as “body goals” among TikTokers, tweeted earlier this year that “i liked my body before I downloaded TikTok.”</quote>
    <link>https://www.vox.com/the-goods/22226997/body-positivity-instagram-tiktok-fatphobia-social-media</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>The Bitcoin Dream Is Dead</title>
    <quote>Bitcoin’s recent 25% plunge illustrates why it will never be a true currency</quote>
    <link>https://marker.medium.com/the-bitcoin-dream-is-dead-8b621d2d7dbd</link>
  </entry>
  
  
</feed>
