<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>March 11, 2016</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Genetic Test Firm to Put Customers’ Data in Public Domain</title>
    <quote>In an unusual move, a leading genetic testing company is putting genetic information from the people it has tested into the public domain, a move the company says could make a large trove of data available to researchers looking for genes linked to various diseases.</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/1LNNI8Z</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>DeepMind founder Demis Hassabis on how AI will shape the future</title>
    <quote>DeepMind’s stunning victories over Go legend Lee Se-dol have stoked excitement over artificial intelligence’s potential more than any event in recent memory. But the Google subsidiary’s AlphaGo program is far from its only project — it’s not even the main one. As co-founder Demis Hassabis said earlier in the week, DeepMind wants to “solve intelligence,” and he has more than a few ideas about how to get there.</quote>
    <link>http://www.theverge.com/2016/3/10/11192774/demis-hassabis-interview-alphago-google-deepmind-ai</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Echo From Amazon Brims With Groundbreaking Promise</title>
    <quote>Yet at the moment, the most promising candidate for the Next Great Gadget isn’t made by Apple, Google, Facebook or Microsoft. Instead, it is the Echo, a screenless, voice-controlled household computer built by Amazon</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/1UdFN6b</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Prototype Mindset</title>
    <quote>A sprint takes place over just five days. On Monday, you unpack a problem you want to solve. On Tuesday, you sketch competing solutions on paper. On Wednesday, you decide how to turn your ideas into a testable hypothesis. On Thursday, you hammer out a prototype. And on Friday, you test it with real live humans.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/galleys/the-prototype-mindset-396c979a356f#.kpnojc6fn</link>
  </entry>
    
  <entry>
    <title>A brief process for more enlightened brainstorming</title>
    <quote>We encourage people to engage in two distinct modes of thinking: divergent thinking, which involves creating choices, and convergent thinking, which involves making choices.</quote>
    <link>http://qz.com/635065</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
