<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>December 15, 2023</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>In historic decision, FDA approves a CRISPR-based medicine for treatment of sickle cell disease</title>
    <quote>The Food and Drug Administration on Friday approved the world’s first medicine based on CRISPR gene-editing technology, a groundbreaking treatment for sickle cell disease that delivers a potential cure for people born with the chronic and life-shortening blood disorder.</quote>
    <link>https://www.statnews.com/2023/12/08/fda-approves-casgevy-crispr-based-medicine-for-treatment-of-sickle-cell-disease/</link>
  </entry>


  <entry>
    <title>How to make Charts for the Movies</title>
    <quote>For Chart Chat #46 we're looking at charts on the big screen. We're joined by Shaun Yue. He's designed the data interfaces for many Hollywood movies, including Skyfall, The Dark Knight, Prometheus and many more. </quote>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yof0wKLRLOk</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Tyler Hobbs on Algorithmic Aesthetics</title>
    <quote>This is the way I like to precisely define where the art is now: it's the potential output space of the generative procedure combined with the curation model.</quote>
    <link>https://www.lerandom.art/editorial/tyler-hobbs-on-algorithmic-aesthetics</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>AI, and everything else</title>
    <quote>Every year, I produce a big presentation exploring macro and strategic trends in the tech industry. For 2024, ‘AI, and everything else’. “In my lifetime, I've seen two demonstrations of technology that struck me as revolutionary...The GUI and ChatGPT”</quote>
    <link>https://www.ben-evans.com/presentations</link>
  </entry>

   <entry>
    <title>Why Vision Pro Will Change Photography</title>
    <quote>Vision Pro opens up opportunities to think about this in more traditional terms — using negative space and the environment with a device like a smartphone can help open up creative opportunities.</quote>
    <link>https://om.co/2023/12/14/why-vision-pro-will-change-photography/</link>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
