<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>July 13, 2018</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Good for your health: design philosophy from the technology of healing</title>
    <quote>A lot of work is being done to bring design thinking to healthcare. I’d like to explore how healthcare can be a source for design philosophy. Not because healthcare has experience design figured out — not by a long shot, obviously. As an industry, healthcare is often rife with misaligned, and even malign incentives that can lead to awful results. But as a discipline of diagnosis, treatment, and prevention, healthcare is the endeavor of healing.</quote>
    <link>https://uxdesign.cc/good-for-your-health-design-philosophy-from-the-technology-of-healing-e467b0883139</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Analytics at work: How Netflix’s Customer Obsession Created a Customer Obsession</title>
    <quote>Reed’s aspiration was that the Netflix team would discover what delights customers through the scientific process — forming hypotheses through existing data, qualitative, and surveys, and then A/B testing these ideas to see what works. His vision was that product leaders at Netflix would develop remarkable consumer insight, fueled by results and learning from thousands of experiments.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/behavior-design/how-netflixs-customer-obsession-created-a-customer-obsession-726c09c2d52b</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Dynamicland</title>
    <quote>Dynamicland is a communal computer, designed for agency, not apps, where people can think like whole humans. -- The computer of the future is not a product, but a place.</quote>
    <link>https://dynamicland.org</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>The App Store turns 10</title>
    <quote>When Apple introduced the App Store on July 10, 2008 with 500 apps, it ignited a cultural, social and economic phenomenon that changed how people work, play, meet, travel and so much more</quote>
    <link>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2018/07/app-store-turns-10/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
</feed>
