<feed>
	<title>Friday Feed</title>
	<date>April 3, 2015</date>
	
	<entry>
		<title>The Healing Power of your own Medical Records</title>
		<quote>At every stage, Mr. Keating, a 26-year-old doctoral student at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology’s Media Lab, has pushed and prodded to get his medical information, collecting an estimated 70 gigabytes of his own patient data by now. His case points to what medical experts say could be gained if patients had full and easier access to their medical information.</quote>
		<link>http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/01/technology/the-healing-power-of-your-own-medical-data.html?_r=0</link>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<title>Scientists have created a Google Maps for the human body</title>
		<quote>Biomedical engineer Melissa Knothe Tate has always thought of the human body as an ecosystem, a world to be discovered. Now, she and a team of researchers have come up with a way to navigate that interior world using Google Maps technology.</quote>
		<link>http://qz.com/372613/scientists-have-created-a-google-maps-for-the-human-body/</link>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Clean up your mess: a guide to visual design for everybody</title>
		<quote>If you're like most people, you feel like a baby when it comes to visual design. You sometimes have a vague sense of what you want, but can't articulate it or make it come about. All you can do is point and cry. This guide will help you communicate with conscious skill. It will show you how to create designs that are easy to understand and attractive.</quote>
		<link>http://visualmess.com/index.html</link>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<title>Design and Redesign</title>
		<quote>Visualization is now a mass medium. It’s not quite Hollywood, but information graphics have millions of viewers, awards ceremonies, and even their own celebrities with tens of thousands of Twitter followers. More important, from the perspective of journalism, is that data visualization is an essential part of the communication process. Today, a data-driven story without a chart is like a fashion story without a photo.</quote>
		<link>https://medium.com/@hint_fm/design-and-redesign-4ab77206cf9</link>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Empowering Design; (Ending the Attention Economy, Talk #1)</title>
		<quote>Our goal: to change the consumer software ecosystem in a deep way. Software shouldn't compete to maximize screentime, but to demonstrate lasting improvements in our lives. We'll work with many fields, but we've started with designers. We're gathering members, giving talks, and running design events around the world.</quote>
		<link>https://vimeo.com/123488311</link>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>How Apple Makes the Watch</title>
		<quote>Apple is the world's foremost manufacturer of goods. At one time, this statement had to be caged and qualified with modifiers such as "consumer goods" or "electronic goods," but last quarter, Apple shipped a Boeing 787's weight worth of iPhones every 24 hours. When we add the rest of the product line to the mix, it becomes clear that Apple's supply chain is one of the largest scale production organizations in the world. </quote>
		<link>http://atomicdelights.com/blog/a-glimpse-at-how-the-apple-watch-is-made</link>
	</entry>
</feed>