<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>February 3, 2023</date>
  
   <entry>
    <title>Layoffs are Cruel and Don't Work</title>
    <quote>Imagine you had a dog. You got the dog when it was young, trained and raised it. This animal was a part of your family and you gave it little collars and cute little clothes with your family name on it. The dog came to special events and soon thought of this place as its home and you all as loved ones. Then one day with no warning, you locked the dog out of the house. You and the other adults in the house had decided getting rid of any random dog was important to the bank that owned your self, so you locked the door. </quote>
    <link>https://matduggan.com/us-layoffs-are-unspeakably-cruel/</link>
  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>The unequal treatment of demographic groups by ChatGPT/OpenAI content moderation system</title>
    <quote>Should AI systems treat different demographic groups unequally?
</quote>
    <link>https://davidrozado.substack.com/p/openaicms</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>ChatGPT Is Dumber Than You Think</title>
    <quote>Treat it like a toy, not a tool.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2022/12/chatgpt-openai-artificial-intelligence-writing-ethics/672386/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hustle bros are jumping on the AI bandwagon</title>
    <quote>The world of financial influencers promise viewers they can use ChatGPT to make big bucks with no effort. The schemes they suggest are dubious, but reveal how the AI chatbot might erode our online world.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2023/2/2/23582772/chatgpt-ai-get-rich-quick-schemes-hustlers-web</link>
  </entry>

    <entry>
    <title>Instagram’s co-founders are back with Artifact, a kind of TikTok for text</title>
    <quote>The app uses algorithmic predictions, which Kevin Systrom sees as ‘the future of social.’</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2023/1/31/23579552/artifact-instagram-cofounders-kevin-systrom-mike-krieger-news-app</link>
  </entry>

 
  
</feed>
