<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>July 14, 2023</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Actors say Hollywood studios want their AI replicas — for free, forever</title>
    <quote>“This ‘groundbreaking’ AI proposal that they gave us yesterday, they proposed that our background performers should be able to be scanned, get one day’s pay, and their companies should own that scan, their image, their likeness and should be able to use it for the rest of eternity on any project they want, with no consent and no compensation.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2023/7/13/23794224/sag-aftra-actors-strike-ai-image-rights</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>A change of typeface: Microsoft’s new default font has arrived</title>
    <quote>He designed the font with a slight humanist touch. He wanted Aptos to have the universal appeal of the late NPR newscaster Carl Kasell and the astute tone of The Late Show host Stephen Colbert. “There’s always that little voice inside of me saying, ‘You know, you gotta try to sneak in a little bit of humanity. </quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/@MicrosoftDesign/a-change-of-typeface-microsofts-new-default-font-has-arrived-f200eb16718d</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>We might have accidentally killed the only life we ever found on Mars nearly 50 years ago</title>
    <quote>In one experiment, the Viking landers added water to Martian soil samples. That might have been a very bad idea.</quote>
    <link>https://bigthink.com/hard-science/accidentally-killed-life-mars/?utm_source=recommendedreads.com</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>ChatGPT: A Bullshit Tool For Bullshit Jobs</title>
    <quote>What else but a bullshit-generating tool to cancel out bullshit-requiring tasks so people can finally fill their lives with something else?</quote>
    <link>https://thealgorithmicbridge.substack.com/p/chatgpt-a-bullshit-tool-for-bullshit</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Seven Rules For Internet CEOs To Avoid Enshittification</title>
    <quote>But if investors are pushing you to make more money now, figure out ways to do that by adding even more value to the world, rather than trying to squeeze your existing community, ripping away the things they love, and telling them you’re doing it for their own good.</quote>
    <link>https://www.techdirt.com/2023/06/21/seven-rules-for-internet-ceos-to-avoid-enshittification/</link>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
