<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>June 24, 2016</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Food Banks Take On a Contributor to Diabetes: Themselves</title>
    <quote>Inconsistent access to food worsens the disease, and so can the offerings at the pantries many low-income people must rely on. Now researchers have begun pursuing innovative new methods to address Type 2 diabetes among people who rely on food banks.</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/1UdxvZm</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
  	<title>Crispr Wins Key Approval to Fight Cancer in Human Trials</title>
  	<quote>Genetic engineering, which for decades never quite lived up to expectations, is being transformed thanks to Crispr. Scientists can use it to manipulate the genes of any living creature with unprecedented ease. Editas Medicine is hoping to begin human trials next year using Crispr to treat a rare form of blindness. The cancer trial approved on Tuesday may come sooner than many in the field had anticipated, and for a broader potential group of patients.</quote>
  	<link>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2016-06-23/crispr-wins-key-approval-to-fight-cancer-in-human-trials</link>
  </entry>
  
   <entry>
    <title>How Google is Remaking Itself as a “Machine Learning First” Company </title>
    <quote>For many years, machine learning was considered a specialty, limited to an elite few. That era is over, as recent results indicate that machine learning, powered by “neural nets” that emulate the way a biological brain operates, is the true path towards imbuing computers with the powers of humans, and in some cases, super humans. Google is committed to expanding that elite within its walls, with the hope of making it the norm. </quote>
    <link>https://backchannel.com/how-google-is-remaking-itself-as-a-machine-learning-first-company-ada63defcb70#.i5u8d6a2g</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Drug Company Lunches Have Big Payoffs</title>
    <quote>A free lunch may be all it takes to persuade a doctor to prescribe a brand-name drug instead of a cheaper generic, a new study suggests.</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/28Jo32k</link>
  </entry>
  
 
  <entry>
    <title>Elegant tools: Why B2B and enterprise design is the next frontier of design impact</title>
    <quote>Facebook's Margaret Stewart shares four key principles for designing quality business products and explains why designing elegant tools may be the highest-impact opportunity that exists for designers today.</quote>
    <link>https://www.oreilly.com/ideas/elegant-tools-why-b2b-and-enterprise-design-is-the-next-frontier-of-design-impact</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Typography for User Interfaces</title>
    <quote>Since my early days in the industry, I’ve grown to love type and all the little nuances that go into setting it. In this article, I want to share some of the fundamentals that I’ve learned, and hopefully help you get better at setting type for user interfaces.</quote>
    <link>https://viljamis.com/2016/typography-for-user-interfaces/</link>
  </entry>

</feed>
