<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>August 26, 2016</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How Parents Harnessed the Power of Social Media to Challenge EpiPen Prices</title>
    <quote>She went online to Petition2Congress.com, a service that collects signatures and then sends them to designated lawmakers, and created the petition “Stop the EpiPen Price Gouging,” which went live on July 11. Then Ms. Kantayya shared the link with her 836 Facebook friends, with a post that began, “Stupid pharmaceutical company!” What happened next is a lesson in the power of social media to create a groundswell, particularly among a group as committed and motivated as the parents of children with food allergies, who must often buy multiple pens for home, school and day care. In just 45 days, Ms. Kantayya’s petition grew from a few dozen signatures to more than 70,000 people who sent more than 100,000 letters to Congress.</quote>
    <link>http://well.blogs.nytimes.com/2016/08/25/how-parents-harnessed-the-power-of-social-media-to-challenge-epipen-prices/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>An Exclusive Look at How AI and Machine Learning Work at Apple</title>
    <quote>Machine learning, my briefers say, is now found all over Apple’s products and services. Apple uses deep learning to detect fraud on the Apple store, to extend battery life between charges on all your devices, and to help it identify the most useful feedback from thousands of reports from its beta testers. Machine learning helps Apple choose news stories for you. It determines whether Apple Watch users are exercising or simply perambulating. It recognizes faces and locations in your photos. It figures out whether you would be better off leaving a weak Wi-Fi signal and switching to the cell network. It even knows what good filmmaking is, enabling Apple to quickly compile your snapshots and videos into a mini-movie at a touch of a button. </quote>
    <link>https://backchannel.com/an-exclusive-look-at-how-ai-and-machine-learning-work-at-apple-8dbfb131932b#.vobc956ws</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Computers trounce pathologists in predicting lung cancer type, severity</title>
    <quote>The researchers found that a machine-learning approach to identifying critical disease-related features accurately differentiated between two types of lung cancers and predicted patient survival times better than the standard approach of pathologists classifying tumors by grade and stage.</quote>
    <link>http://med.stanford.edu/news/all-news/2016/08/computers-trounce-pathologists-in-predicting-lung-cancer-severity.html</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>If you don't pay attention, data can drive you off a cliff </title>
    <quote>You’re a hotshot manager. You love your dashboards and you keep your finger on the beating pulse of the business. You take pride in using data to drive your decisions rather than shooting from the hip like one of those old-school 1950s bosses. This is the 21st century, and data is king. You even hired a sexy statistician or data scientist, though you don’t really understand what they do. Never mind, you can proudly tell all your friends that you are leading a modern data-driven team. Nothing can go wrong, right?</quote>
    <link>https://yanirseroussi.com/2016/08/21/seven-ways-to-be-data-driven-off-a-cliff/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Eleven Reasons To Be Excited About The Future of Technology</title>
    <quote>Self-driving cars, Clean Energy, Virtual and Augmented Reality, Drones and Flying Cars, Artificial Intelligence, Pocket Supercomputers for Everyone, Cryptocurrencies and Blockchains, High-Quality Online Education, Better Food through Science, Computerized Medicine, A New Space Age</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/@cdixon/eleven-reasons-to-be-excited-about-the-future-of-technology-ef5f9b939cb2#.7v3i1nds2</link>
  </entry>
  

</feed>
