<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>September 4, 2015</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>New Alternatives to Statins Add to a Quandary on Cholesterol</title>
    <quote>“We’ve reached a point where patients are increasingly facing five- and six-figure price tags for medications that they will take over the course of their lifetimes,” said Matthew Eyles, an executive vice president for America’s Health Insurance Plans, the national trade association for the insurance industry. “If this is the new normal to treat common and chronic conditions, how can any health system sustain that cost?”</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/1LJPuXy</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>When PCSK9 Inhibitors Compete</title>
    <quote>t is estimated that between 5 and 10 million Americans currently live with these forms of high cholesterol. Even with their limited initial indications, PCSK9 inhibitors have the potential to grow over the next several years to become the costliest therapy class our country has seen.</quote>
    <link>http://lab.express-scripts.com/insights/drug-options/when-pcsk9-inhibitors-compete</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Why a few unvaccinated children are an even bigger threat than you think</title>
    <quote>The sad truth is this: as long as there are communities that harbor strong negative views about vaccination, there will be outbreaks of vaccine-preventable diseases in those communities. These outbreaks will happen even if the population as a whole has achieved the vaccination coverage considered sufficient for herd immunity.</quote>
    <link>http://wapo.st/1Da0zvm</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Design the Beginning</title>
    <quote>Nobody cares about the thing you’ve designed, unless you can get them past the beginning.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/the-year-of-the-looking-glass/design-the-beginning-b8e61081ce42</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Mobile:2015 UI / UX Trends</title>
    <quote>Whether on an app screen, a web browser, or a wearable watch face, design is one of the most important drivers of consumer engagement. From flat design to Material design, I analysed what trends have evolved, and share a few of my insights with you — what are these trends? Why are they beneficial to the user? And how are they created?</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/interactive-mind/mobile-2015-263ab694e60e</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
