<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>July 7, 2023</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Spill Is a New Black-Owned Twitter Alternative. Here’s What to Know About the App</title>
    <quote>Spill is being designed by diverse developers who are programming the artificial intelligence on the platform to monitor abuse or hate against communities of color. “Everybody who’s in Black Twitter or any of these other communities knows that it’s powered by Black women. Setting all the trends and all of that is part of that, but also getting way more hate than any other group. It’s actually insane, when you actually look at it statistically. </quote>
    <link>https://time.com/6292622/spill-app-twitter-alternative/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why Instagram is taking on Twitter with Threads</title>
    <quote>The ‘volatility’ of Twitter under Elon Musk has opened a window to compete. It’s a ‘risky’ bet worth trying, says Instagram boss Adam Mosseri.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2023/7/5/23784870/instagram-threads-adam-mosseri-interview-twitter-competitor</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Authors file a lawsuit against OpenAI for unlawfully ‘ingesting’ their books</title>
    <quote>Two authors have filed a lawsuit against OpenAI, the company behind the artificial intelligence tool ChatGPT, claiming that the organisation breached copyright law by “training” its model on novels without the permission of authors.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theguardian.com/books/2023/jul/05/authors-file-a-lawsuit-against-openai-for-unlawfully-ingesting-their-books</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>France set to allow police to spy through phones</title>
    <quote>French police should be able to spy on suspects by remotely activating the camera, microphone and GPS of their phones and other devices, lawmakers agreed late on Wednesday, July 5. Part of a wider justice reform bill, the spying provision has been attacked by both the left and rights defenders as an authoritarian snoopers' charter, though Justice Minister Éric Dupond-Moretti insists it would affect only "dozens of cases a year."</quote>
    <link>https://www.lemonde.fr/en/france/article/2023/07/06/france-set-to-allow-police-to-spy-through-phones_6044269_7.html</link>
  </entry>


 <entry>
    <title>GUINNESS WORLD RECORD Fourth Of July Drone Show! (1,000+ Drones)</title>
    <quote>This Fourth of July, history was made. Sky Elements Drone Shows achieved the GUINNESS WORLD RECORDS™ title for the largest aerial sentence formed by multirotor/drones. 1,002 drones armed with bright LED lights took flight and dazzled the crowd with a show paying tribute to the history of the United States.  </quote>
    <link>https://youtu.be/zdOTV2RH9IY</link>
  </entry>

  
</feed>
