<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>June 18, 2021</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Winners and Losers of the Work-From-Home Revolution</title>
    <quote>High-income workers at highly profitable companies will benefit greatly. Downtown landlords won’t.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/06/winners-losers-work-home-remote/619181/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>When Graphs Are a Matter of Life and Death</title>
    <quote>Pie charts and scatter plots seem like ordinary tools, but they revolutionized the way we solve problems.</quote>
    <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/06/21/when-graphs-are-a-matter-of-life-and-death</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>What If Doctors Are Always Watching, but Never There?</title>
    <quote> The child’s death left us shaken, with one question hanging like a dagger in the room: What could we have done to notice his decline sooner—while he was still just edging toward the precipice, and not after he had started the steep, downward slide?</quote>
    <link>https://www.wired.com/story/can-remote-tech-save-lives/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The coming productivity boom</title>
    <quote>When you put these three factors together—the bounty of technological advances, the compressed restructuring timetable due to covid-19, and an economy finally running at full capacity—the ingredients are in place for a productivity boom.</quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/06/10/1026008/the-coming-productivity-boom/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Document Culture of Amazon</title>
    <quote>Reading documents is so ingrained in our culture and process that our scheduling tools have check boxes to automatically create a document. If I’m catching up on a new service or feature launch, I will find the document rather than emailing or calling the product manager.</quote>
    <link>https://www.justingarrison.com/blog/2021-03-15-the-document-culture-of-amazon/</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
