<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>April 14, 2017</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Tackling Weight Loss and Diabetes With Video Chats</title>
    <quote>“Developing remote care models is going to be the key if we’re going to have some sort of impact on improving glucose control for the millions of people with diabetes,” he said. “It’s a much more scalable model than seeing people in a doctor’s office.”</quote>
    <link>https://nyti.ms/2oliJrN</link>
  </entry>
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Can “Digital Therapeutics” Be as Good as Drugs?</title>
    <quote>Digital therapeutics, or “digiceuticals,” as some call them, have become a Holy Grail in some quarters of Silicon Valley, where investors see the chance to deliver medicine through your smartphone. Andreessen Horowitz, the venture firm, even predicts digital drugs will become “the third phase” of medicine, meaning the successor to the chemical and protein drugs we have now, but without the billion-dollar cost of bringing one to market.  </quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/604053/can-digital-therapeutics-be-as-good-as-drugs</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Bezos Says Artificial Intelligence to Fuel Amazon's Success</title>
    <quote>Bezos repeated familiar themes, such as the need to operate a business like it’s always “Day 1” to keep a startup mentality and the ability to act quickly on limited information to stay ahead, what he calls “high-velocity decision making.” His emphasis on artificial intelligence and machine learning was the most concrete indication of areas in which the e-commerce giant will continue to invest.</quote>
    <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2017-04-12/bezos-says-artificial-intelligence-to-fuel-amazon-s-success</link>
  </entry>
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>FDA Opens Genetic Floodgates with 23andMe Decision</title>
    <quote>“Consumers can now have direct access to certain genetic risk information,” said Jeffrey Shuren, director of the FDA’s Center for Devices and Radiological Health, in a statement. “But it is important that people understand that genetic risk is just one piece of the bigger puzzle. It does not mean they will or won’t ultimately develop a disease.”</quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/604109/fda-opens-genetic-floodgates-with-23andme-decision</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>I’m Not Texting. I’m Taking Notes.</title>
    <quote>But when he started to get into specifics, I noticed that other people were pulling out their laptops and notepads. I knew I had better take notes, so I reached for my phone. That’s what I like to use....“Many board members noticed that you were on your phone a lot,” he said. “If you can hold out on texting friends or checking your Twitter feed until the breaks, that would be great.”</quote>
    <link>https://nyti.ms/2obdcpi</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
