<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>March 19, 2021</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Who Is Making Sure the A.I. Machines Aren’t Racist?</title>
    <quote>When Google forced out two well-known artificial intelligence experts, a long-simmering research controversy burst into the open.</quote>
    <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/03/15/technology/artificial-intelligence-google-bias.html</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Buzzy, Chatty, Out-of-Control Rise of Clubhouse</title>
    <quote>Paul Davison and Rohan Seth’s audio-only app is the tech crush of the pandemic. Now comes the hard part: hosting a global gabfest, without the toxicity.</quote>
    <link>https://www.wired.com/story/inside-clubhouse-audio-app-paul-davison-rohan-seth/</link>
  </entry>
 
  <entry>
    <title>The uneasy intimacy of work in a pandemic year</title>
    <quote>How capitalism and the pandemic destroyed our work-life balance.</quote>
    <link>https://www.vox.com/culture/22308547/pandemic-anniversary-labor-works-intimacy-how-to-do-nothing</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The End of Silicon Valley as We Know It?</title>
    <quote>the inventions we most urgently need will take us in a very different direction than the consumer internet and social media revolution that is coming to an unsightly end.</quote>
    <link>https://www.oreilly.com/radar/the-end-of-silicon-valley-as-we-know-it/</link>
  </entry>

   <entry>
    <title>Photographer Spends 12 Years, 1250 Hours, Exposing Photo of Milky Way</title>
    <quote>Finnish astrophotographer J-P Metsavainio has released a Milky Way photo that took him nearly 12 years to create. The 1.7-gigapixel image has a cumulative exposure time of 1,250 hours.</quote>
    <link>https://petapixel.com/2021/03/16/photographer-spends-12-years-1250-hours-exposing-photo-of-milky-way/</link>
  </entry>
  

  <entry>
    <title>A Pandemic Winner: How Zoom Beat Tech Giants To Dominate Video Chat</title>
    <quote>Looking back, the 9-to-5, everybody needs to be in the same place at the same time during that window so you can pound on a computer for eight hours straight — that's in our rear view mirror</quote>
    <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/03/19/978393310/a-pandemic-winner-how-zoom-beat-tech-giants-to-dominate-video-chat</link>
  </entry>
  
  </feed>