<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>January 28, 2022</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Searching for Susy Thunder</title>
    <quote>In the ’80s, Susan Headley ran with the best of them—phone phreakers, social engineers, and the most notorious computer hackers of the era. Then she disappeared.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/c/22889425/susy-thunder-headley-hackers-phone-phreakers-claire-evans</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>I’ve seen the metaverse – and I don’t want it</title>
    <quote>Unfortunately, nothing I have experienced in any virtual world makes me feel good about the idea of the metaverse – because it is being constructed by people to whom the problems of the real world are mostly invisible.</quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Cory Doctorow: Science Fiction is a Luddite Literature</title>
    <quote>In truth, the Luddites’ cause wasn’t the destruction of technology – no more than the Boston Tea Party’s cause was the elimination of tea, or Al Qaeda’s cause was the end of civilian aviation. Smashing looms and stocking frames was the Luddites’ tactic, not their goal.</quote>
    <link>https://locusmag.com/2022/01/cory-doctorow-science-fiction-is-a-luddite-literature/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>James Webb Space Telescope arrives at new home in space</title>
    <quote>“Webb, welcome home!” said NASA Administrator Bill Nelson. “Congratulations to the team for all of their hard work ensuring Webb’s safe arrival at L2 today. We’re one step closer to uncovering the mysteries of the universe. And I can’t wait to see Webb’s first new views of the universe this summer!”</quote>
    <link>https://www.space.com/james-webb-arrives-destination-l2</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>The science of masks, explained by a mechanical engineer after 2 years of testing in his lab</title>
    <quote>As the CDC changes its guidelines to recommend more heavy-duty masks, this scientist explains what’s behind the difference in quality of cloth masks, surgical masks, and N95s—and how to make them the most effective.
</quote>
    <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90716689/the-science-of-masks-explained-by-a-mechanical-engineer-after-2-years-of-testing-in-his-lab</link>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
