<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>March 26, 2021</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>End Meeting for All</title>
    <quote>When we remember this time, we’ll do so through a bunch of little boxes on a laptop screen. The photographer Thomas Dworzak captured our strange, sad year on Zoom.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2021/03/our-year-on-zoom-a-photo-essay/618306/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What Data Can’t Do</title>
    <quote>When it comes to people—and policy—numbers are both powerful and perilous.</quote>
    <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/03/29/what-data-cant-do</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Finance Citigroup CEO Jane Fraser calls for Zoom-Free Fridays and new bank holiday as pandemic fatigue grows</title>
    <quote>The blurring of lines between home and work and the relentlessness of the pandemic workday have taken a toll on our well-being,” Fraser said in the memo. “It’s simply not sustainable. Since a return to any kind </quote>
    <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/23/citigroup-ceo-jane-fraser-calls-for-zoom-free-fridays.html</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Uptime 15,364 days - The Computers of Voyager</title>
    <quote>This talk explores the computing systems of Voyager - the systems which enable remote control of the spacecraft, and provide for the recording and return of data to Earth. These systems have proved to be both adaptable, durable, and resilient in support of a scientific undertaking now in it's fifth decade.</quote>
    <link>https://youtu.be/H62hZJVqs2o</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Part of Wright brothers' 1st airplane on NASA's Mars chopper</title>
    <quote>NASA's experimental Martian helicopter holds a small swatch of fabric from the 1903 Wright Flyer, the space agency revealed Tuesday. The helicopter, named Ingenuity, hitched a ride to the red planet with the Perseverance rover, arriving last month.</quote>
    <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-03-wright-brothers-1st-airplane-nasa.html</link>
  </entry>

</feed>
