
<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>April 8, 2022</date>


  <entry>
    <title>Leaked: New Amazon Worker Chat App Would Ban Words Like “union,” “restrooms,” “pay Raise,” And “plantation”</title>
    <quote>An automatic word monitor would also block a variety of terms that could represent potential critiques of Amazon’s working conditions, like “slave labor,” “prison,” and “plantation,” as well as “restrooms”</quote>
    <link>https://theintercept.com/2022/04/04/amazon-union-living-wage-restrooms-chat-app/</link>
  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>One App, Two Worlds</title>
    <quote>In two cities, close geographically, TikTok shows two world views</quote>
    <link>https://www.nrk.no/osloogviken/xl/tiktok-doesn_t-show-the-war-in-ukraine-to-russian-users-1.15921522</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The weird computers and claustrophobic hallways of Severance</title>
    <quote>At first glance, the offices in Severance look fairly normal. They’re brightly lit with clean white walls and carpeted green floors. But in the macrodata refinement wing — where much of the show takes place — things are a little off. </quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/23013413/severance-apple-tv-plus-production-design-computers</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>These 3-Michelin-starred plates were invented by AI. The food doesn’t even exist</title>
    <quote>“It’s almost like an alien life form observed us and tried to imitate and blend in the best it could, without really understanding what is going on,” Stefaner says. “This ‘strangely familiar unfamiliar’ feeling is a bit unsettling, but can also really trigger creativity. </quote>
    <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90739239/these-3-star-michelin-plates-were-invented-by-ai-the-food-doesnt-even-exist</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Workflow Breakdown of Every 2022 Oscars Best Picture Nominee</title>
    <quote>this deep dive gives you all the details about what it takes to create an award-worthy movie.</quote>
    <link>https://blog.frame.io/2022/03/28/oscars-2022-best-picture-workflows/</link>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
