<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>June 14, 2019</date>

  <entry>
    <title>Internet Trends 2019</title>
    <quote>The annual Mary Meeker report: Besides the usual trends: Some 51 percent of the world — 3.8 billion people — were internet users last year, up from 49 percent (3.6 billion) in 2017, and Americans are spending more time with digital media than ever: 6.3 hours a day in 2018, up 7 percent from the year before, note the healthcare section -- "Digital Impact expanding across the ecosystem"</quote>
    <link>https://www.bondcap.com/report/itr19/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>CRISPR scientists are teaming up with a pharma giant to look for new drug clues</title>
    <quote>GlaxoSmithKline will pour $67 million into a new laboratory at the University of California to industrialize the search for drug clues using the gene-editing tool CRISPR.</quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/f/613769/for-drug-industry-the-prescription-is-more-crispr/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Benchling: Evolving to Enterprise-Grade Permissions</title>
    <quote>Benchling is a data platform to help scientists do research. Hundreds of thousands of scientists across academic labs and enterprise companies use Benchling to store and analyze scientific data, record notes, and share findings with each other.</quote>
    <link>https://benchling.engineering/evolving-to-enterprise-grade-permissions-493eac166449</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>How 5 Data Dynamos Do Their Jobs</title>
    <quote>Our news reporters are increasingly choosing to level-up their data skills as well in order to find stories hidden in the numbers, organize their reporting and check government conclusions. The demand for this knowledge has been so great that our digital transition team now runs a training program to help reporters work on these skills.</quote>
    <link>https://nyti.ms/2MF0s8q</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
</feed>
