<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>October 11, 2019</date>

  <entry>
    <title>A Patient Hopes Gene-Editing Can Help With Pain Of Sickle Cell Disease</title>
    <quote>Scientists used CRISPR to modify a gene in the cells to make them produce fetal hemoglobin, a protein that babies usually stop making shortly after birth. The hope is that the protein produced through the gene-editing treatment will give sickle cell patients like Gray healthy red blood cells.</quote>
    <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2019/10/10/766765780/after-a-life-of-painful-sickle-cell-disease-a-patient-hopes-gene-editing-can-hel</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>‘Treatise’: A Visual Symphony Of Information Design</title>
    <quote>Why Cornelius Cardew’s legendary 193-page graphic score might not actually be about music</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/nightingale/treatise-a-visual-symphony-of-information-design-2ced33ef01a0</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Any Sufficiently Advanced Neglect is Indistinguishable from Malice, Assumptions and Bias in Algorithmic Systems</title>
    <quote> I want to spend time on it because I think what doesn’t get through in many of our discussions is that it’s not just about how Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning, or Algorithmic instances get trained, but the processes for how and the cultural environments in which HUMANS are increasingly taught/shown/environmentally encouraged/socialized to think is the “right way” to build and train said systems.</quote>
    <link>http://www.afutureworththinkingabout.com/?p=5442</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>150 successful machine learning models: 6 lessons learned at Booking.com</title>
    <quote>We found that driving true business impact is amazingly hard, plus it is difficult to isolate and understand the connection between efforts on modeling and the observed impact… Our main conclusion is that an iterative, hypothesis driven process, integrated with other disciplines was fundamental to build 150 successful products enabled by machine learning.</quote>
    <link>https://blog.acolyer.org/2019/10/07/150-successful-machine-learning-models/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Eight Habits of Expert Software Designers: An Illustrated Guide</title>
    <quote>volve the user, design elegant abstractions, focus on the essence, simulate continually, look around, reshape the problem space, see error as opportunity, think about what they are not designing</quote>
    <link>https://thereader.mitpress.mit.edu/habits-of-expert-software-designers/</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
