<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>April 22, 2022</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Monopoly On Your Mind, Part 1: Consolidation Craze and Illusion of Choice</title>
    <quote>Today, Comcast, Disney, AT&amp;T, Sony, Fox, and Paramount Global control 90% of what you watch, read, or listen to.</quote>
    <link>https://rebeccastrong.substack.com/p/big-media-big-conflicts-of-interest?s=r</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why it’s so damn hard to make AI fair and unbiased</title>
    <quote>There are competing notions of fairness — and sometimes they’re totally incompatible with each other.</quote>
    <link>https://www.vox.com/future-perfect/22916602/ai-bias-fairness-tradeoffs-artificial-intelligence</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>You can now buy a Framework mainboard and turn it into the weird computer of your dreams</title>
    <quote>But making the mainboard available separately could also be a way to kickstart a different kind of ecosystem, in which users and developers can build different kinds of computers altogether starting from Framework’s template.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2022/4/22/23037156/framework-mainboard-marketplace-intel</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Intel calls its AI that detects student emotions a teaching tool. Others call it 'morally reprehensible.'</title>
    <quote>“Students shouldn’t have to police how they look in the classroom,” said Nandita Sampath, a policy analyst with Consumer Reports focused on algorithmic bias and accountability issues, who said she wondered whether students would have the ability to contest inaccurate results if Intel’s system leads to negative consequences. “What cognitive and emotional states do these companies claim they are able to assess or predict, and what is the accountability?”</quote>
    <link>https://www.protocol.com/enterprise/emotion-ai-school-intel-edutech</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>I recreated the @netflix intro with $30 worth of yarn</title>
    <quote>Check the full video is here</quote>
    <link>https://twitter.com/kevinbparry/status/1517199587886387201</link>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
