<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>January 5, 2018</date>

  <entry>
    <title>Reading privileged memory with a side-channel</title>
    <quote>We have discovered that CPU data cache timing can be abused to efficiently leak information out of mis-speculated execution, leading to (at worst) arbitrary virtual memory read vulnerabilities across local security boundaries in various contexts.</quote>
    <link>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2018/01/reading-privileged-memory-with-side.html</link>
  </entry>

   <entry>
    <title>Meltdown and Spectre: Patches, mitigations, and microcode</title>
    <quote>Meltdown, applicable to virtually every Intel chip made for many years, along with certain high-performance ARM designs, is the easier to exploit and enables any user program to read vast tracts of kernel data. Spectre, applicable to chips from Intel, AMD, and ARM, and probably every other processor on the market that offers speculative execution too, is more subtle. It encompasses a trick testing array bounds to read memory within a single process, which can be used to attack the integrity of virtual machines and sandboxes.</quote>
    <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2018/01/meltdown-and-spectre-heres-what-intel-apple-microsoft-others-are-doing-about-it/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>AI and Deep Learning in 2017 – A Year in Review</title>
    <quote>2017 saw many bold claims about Deep Learning techniques solving medical problems and beating human experts. There was a lot of hype, and understanding true breakthroughs is anything but easy for someone not coming from a medical background. For an comprehensive review, I recommend Luke Oakden-Rayner’s The End of Human Doctors blog post series.</quote>
    <link>http://www.wildml.com/2017/12/ai-and-deep-learning-in-2017-a-year-in-review/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>10 predictions for deep learning in 2018</title>
    <quote>The incredible breakthroughs we saw in 2017 for deep learning will carry over in a very powerful way in 2018. A lot of work coming from 2017’s research will migrate into everyday software applications.</quote>
    <link>https://venturebeat.com/2018/01/02/10-predictions-for-deep-learning-in-2018/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>The Biggest Technology Failures of 2017</title>
    <quote>Among them are: Do it Yourself Gene Therapy, Trump’s Twitter, Juicero and “Internet freedom”</quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/609626/the-biggest-technology-failures-of-2017/</link>
  </entry>
  
 
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
</feed>
