<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>May 21, 2021</date>

  <entry>
    <title>Amazon’s Ring is the largest civilian surveillance network the US has ever seen</title>
    <quote>One in 10 US police departments can now access videos from millions of privately owned home security cameras without a warrant</quote>
    <link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2021/may/18/amazon-ring-largest-civilian-surveillance-network-us</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Someone mailed an AirTag to themselves to see if they could track its route</title>
    <quote>Apple's AirTag item tracker is now on sale and people are already putting them through their paces. But just how accurate is the tracking capability of the little plastic pucks? That's something Dutch YouTuber AirtagAlex wanted to find out, so they mailed an AirTag to themselves and watched it work its way through the Dutch mail service.</quote>
    <link>https://www.imore.com/someone-mailed-airtag-themselves-see-if-they-could-track-its-route</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Distribution and Demand</title>
    <quote>Cable mogul John Malone, a major Discovery shareholder, said that although he believes Time Warner is doing fine, merging content and distribution usually doesn’t make sense. “I think that the technology of connectivity and digital technologies are one focus, and creating content that people get addicted to is another focus,” he said. “And you seldom would find both of those in the same management team.”</quote>
    <link>https://stratechery.com/2021/distribution-and-demand/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Unequal Scenes</title>
    <quote>Unequal Scenes uses a drone to illustrate the inscribed history of our world in a new way. The scars within our urban fabric, so apparent from above, can provoke a sense of surprise…But also reveal our complicity in systematic disenfranchisement.</quote>
    <link>https://unequalscenes.com/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Metric Display Standards</title>
    <quote>Best practices for presenting numbers that change with time</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/salesforce-ux/metric-display-standards-54736533c81</link>
  </entry>

  
  

</feed>
