<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>December 18, 2015</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>In a New Approach to Fighting Disease, Helpful Genetic Mutations Are Sought</title>
    <quote>So Mr. Whitney has become Exhibit A in a new direction in genetics research. After years of looking for mutations that cause diseases, investigators are now searching for those that prevent them. By understanding how protective mutations work, they hope to develop drugs that mimic them and protect everyone.</quote>
    <link>http://nyti.ms/1y02HEY</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>SLACK AND THE STATE OF TECHNOLOGY AT THE END OF 2015</title>
    <quote>What matters — what always matters! — is what actual users want to do, and what jobs they want to accomplish. And, whatever they want to do almost certainly involves communicating, which means Slack and its competitors are the best-placed to be the foundational platform of the cloud epoch. More broadly, humans are social creatures: why should we be surprised that social networks are primed to be the most important businesseses of all?</quote>
    <link>https://stratechery.com/2015/slack-and-the-state-of-technology-in-2015/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Slack Platform Launch</title>
    <quote>The Slack Platform aims to make your experience with apps even better. We know that just a fraction of improvement in everyday interactions between the business services you use makes a world of difference. And so today we’re taking a few bigs steps forward in bringing them all together.</quote>
    <link>http://slackhq.com/post/134878632730/launch-platform</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>A Purpose-built Global Network: Google's Move to Software-Defined Networking</title>
    <quote>So this is the story of what Google ended up doing to get out of the box it found itself in with its backbone network. Spoiler alert: SDNs (software-defined networks) have played a major role. Amin Vahdat, Google's tech lead for networking, helps us tell the story of how that's all played out. He's both a Distinguished Engineer and a Google Fellow. Somehow he also manages to find time to teach at UC San Diego and Duke.</quote>
    <link>http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=2856460</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Inflamed</title>
    <quote>Paul Ridker, a cardiovascular expert and a colleague of Libby’s at Harvard and Brigham and Women’s, moved the research beyond the laboratory. He found that many patients who’d had heart attacks, despite lacking factors such as high blood pressure, high cholesterol, and a history of smoking, had an elevated level of C-reactive protein, a molecule produced in response to inflammation, in their blood.</quote>
    <link>http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2015/11/30/inflamed</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
</feed>
