<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>August 13, 2021</date>

  <entry>
    <title>End of the line for Uber</title>
    <quote>Uber is a bezzle ("the magic interval when a confidence trickster knows he has the money he has appropriated but the victim does not yet understand that he has lost it"). Every bezzle ends.</quote>
    <link>https://pluralistic.net/2021/08/10/unter/#bezzle-no-more</link>
  </entry>

   <entry>
    <title>Gazing at the Mother Tongue</title>
    <quote>Analyzing Twitter’s Image Cropping Algorithm on Bilingual Memes: Her experiment shows how the algorithm favors cropping Latin scripts over Arabic scripts and what this means in terms of harms to linguistic diversity and representation online.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/taraaz/gazing-at-the-mother-tongue-854c9e89b422</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The IBM PC, 41 Years Ago</title>
    <quote>But in August 1980, one year earlier, IBM started putting together the design of the IBM PC. If that (one year) sounds like an awfully short development cycle for a product like the PC, that’s because it was, especially for a company like IBM where the typical product development cycle was closer to five years at the time. The tight schedule determined the PC design: No custom or not yet available chips, no major software development, favor proven and familiar technologies.</quote>
    <link>https://www.os2museum.com/wp/the-ibm-pc-41-years-ago/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Nvidia Reveals Its CEO Was Computer Generated in Keynote Speech</title>
    <quote>Nvidia pulled off a stunt to promote and showcase its latest technology by digitizing its CEO Jensen Huang in a conference keynote.</quote>
    <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/88nbpa/nvidia-reveals-its-ceo-was-computer-generated-in-keynote-speech</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Tiny tools and the ephemeral nature of digital art…</title>
    <quote>I think it’s fascinating how certain art will outlive the tools it was made in, or some tools will outlive the art… with formats once supported in that tool just dying out and no longer being something you can even see.</quote>
    <link>http://www.nathalielawhead.com/candybox/tiny-tools-and-the-ephemeral-nature-of-digital-art</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
