<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>February 18, 2022</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>A new map of NYC’s cameras shows more surveillance in Black and brown neighborhoods</title>
    <quote>An Amnesty International report on exposure to facial recognition documents the location of 25,500 cameras in New York, revealing that areas with more surveillance have higher rates of “stop-and-frisk” police searches.</quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/2022/02/14/1045333/map-nyc-cameras-surveillance-bias-facial-recognition/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Don't point out something wrong immediately</title>
    <quote>Think about how to deliver the feedback before actually doing it. This "pause" is easier said than done, because of the strong habit we have formed over the years.</quote>
    <link>https://blog.the-pans.com/wrong/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Dad takes down town's internet by mistake to get his kids offline</title>
    <quote>A French dad faces jail time and a hefty fine after using a signal jammer to prevent his kids from going online and taking the rest of a nearby town down with them.</quote>
    <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/dad-takes-down-towns-internet-by-mistake-to-get-his-kids-offline/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Tumblr is 15</title>
    <quote>A bratty teenager at heart, Tumblr has remained the same hellsite you’ve always made it: with your faves, aesthetics, and fandoms, your blogs and sideblogs, your reblog chains and tag conversations. Some of you will have been here for The Dress and the ball pit; some of you know those as lore but only come here for the sexymen and, idk, bees, the bee movie. And you’re all valid.</quote>
    <link>https://best-of-reblogs.tumblr.com/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Happy 15th birthday Hacker News</title>
    <quote>Stories from February 19, 2007</quote>
    <link>https://news.ycombinator.com/front?day=2007-02-19</link>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
