<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>February 16, 2018</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The workplaces of the future will be more human, not less</title>
    <quote>In an age when the ability to think and learn, to process and reason take centre stage, the coming age of automation means that, in order to thrive in the modern workplace, we must become more human.</quote>
    <link>http://www.wired.co.uk/article/learn-to-code-future-of-work</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>“We’re in a diversity crisis”: cofounder of Black in AI on what’s poisoning algorithms in our lives</title>
    <quote>There is a bias to what kinds of problems we think are important, what kinds of research we think are important, and where we think AI should go. If we don’t have diversity in our set of researchers, we are not going to address problems that are faced by the majority of people in the world. </quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/610192/were-in-a-diversity-crisis-black-in-ais-founder-on-whats-poisoning-the-algorithms-in-our</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Inside The Two Years That Shook Facebook—And The World</title>
    <quote>How a confused, defensive social media giant steered itself into a disaster, and how Mark Zuckerberg is trying to fix it all.</quote>
    <link>https://www.wired.com/story/inside-facebook-mark-zuckerberg-2-years-of-hell/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>12 Mobile UX Design Trends For 2018</title>
    <quote>User Journey Simplification, in-app Gestures Paired With Animation, Content-Centered Experience, and Full-Screen Experiences, Vibrant Colors, Emotional Experiences, Dominance of Video, Biometric Authentication, Conversational Design, Advanced Personalization, Augmented Reality, Cashless Payments</quote>
    <link>https://uxplanet.org/12-mobile-ux-design-trends-for-2018-5b4ce7e8445f</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>New CRISPR tools can detect infections like HPV, dengue, and Zika</title>
    <quote>Together, these two papers prove the enormous potential behind different versions of CRISPR — and not just to edit genomes. “It enables a new generation of diagnostics that may be more widely available and more cost effective than current technologies,”</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2018/2/15/17012866/crispr-detectr-sherlock-zika-dengue-hpv-diagnostic-tools</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
