<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>January 7, 2022</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>NASA successfully deploys complex sunshield on James Webb Space Telescope</title>
    <quote>But in order to observe the ancient Universe, JWST has to go through a complex unfolding process first. The telescope was far too large to launch to space in its final configuration, so mission designers crafted the telescope to unfold after launch. The deployment relies on hundreds of mechanisms and moving parts, and everything has to go right in order for JWST to function.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2022/1/4/22857571/nasa-jwst-space-telescope-sunshield-deployment-success</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Crytpo Fundamentals and NFTs</title>
    <quote>Just another fad or the next big thing?</quote>
    <link>https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1sUpk0gbvRQelH0MUIOqjNeGe8nwRH4mhrhDHmI6qh4M/mobilepresent?slide=id.g442eb61d9d_0_0</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Tek Fog: An App With BJP Footprints for Cyber Troops to Automate Hate, Manipulate Trends</title>
    <quote>Over a series of tweets in April 2020, an anonymous Twitter account @Aarthisharma08 claiming to be a disgruntled employee of the Bharatiya Janata Party's (BJP's) Information Technology Cell (IT Cell) alleged the existence of a highly sophisticated and secret app called 'Tek Fog'. They claimed this app is used by political operatives affiliated with the ruling party to artificially inflate the popularity of the party, harass its critics and manipulate public perceptions at scale across major social media platforms.</quote>
    <link>https://thewire.in/tekfog/en/1.html</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Does Data Visualization Have Rules? Or Is It All Just “It Depends”?</title>
    <quote>Deliberately breaking rules for artistic reasons can be extremely effective, but breaking them because you didn’t know about them in the first place will reliably produce charts that are unobvious, confusing, ambiguous, and/or misleading,</quote>
    <link>https://nightingaledvs.com/does-data-visualization-have-rules-or-is-it-all-just-it-depends/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>The Theranos trial was a pop culture phenomenon</title>
    <quote>Writers and producers were quick to recognize the public’s captivation in Holmes, documenting her rise and fall in successful books, podcasts, and television shows. Wall Street Journal reporter John Carreyou wrote a book, Bad Blood, based on the investigation that led to criminal proceedings, and has been documenting the trial in a podcast. ABC News’s The Dropout, which has also been following the story, is currently among the top 50 Apple podcasts in the US.</quote>
    <link>https://qz.com/2109336/how-elizabeth-holmes-became-a-pop-culture-phenomenon/</link>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
