<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>November 3, 2017</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Forget The 10,000-Hour Rule; Edison, Bezos, &amp; Zuckerberg Follow The 10,000-Experiment Rule</title>
    <quote>As you go through your day, following the 10,000-experiment rule means constantly looking for opportunities to collect data rather than just doing what you need to do. It means adding a deliberate reflection process based on reviewing data before the day ends.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/the-mission/forget-about-the-10-000-hour-rule-7b7a39343523</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Pitching a product idea</title>
    <quote>(1) Describe the problem you’re solving, (2) Describe how many people have this problem. (3) Talk about the solution in terms of the experience, not the product. (4) Let go of “mine” or “yours”, embrace “ours”</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/the-year-of-the-looking-glass/pitching-a-product-idea-7566dd85c745</link>
  </entry>
  
  
   <entry>
    <title>Why Computers Should Be Hidden</title>
    <quote>The joy I used to feel when using computers has turned largely to anguish. These machines once provided a unique and compelling way to do things, from writing to shopping to communication to entertainment. But today, devices and services strive to replace every activity with computer use itself. Now I think about escaping the computer as much as using it.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2017/10/why-computers-should-be-hidden/543903/</link>
  </entry>

 <entry>
    <title>The Improbable Origins of PowerPoint</title>
    <quote>PowerPoint is so ingrained in modern life that the notion of it having a history at all may seem odd. But it does have a very definite lifetime as a commercial product that came onto the scene 30 years ago, in 1987. Remarkably, the founders of the Silicon Valley firm that created PowerPoint did not set out to make presentation software, let alone build a tool that would transform group communication throughout the world.</quote>
    <link>https://spectrum.ieee.org/tech-history/cyberspace/the-improbable-origins-of-powerpoint</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Review: iPhone X</title>
    <quote>Disneyland is a vacation spot that has you using your iPhone like crazy every day. You take pictures, you look up directions, you use it for ticketing and FastPasses for rides. It’s hot and you’re distracted, and if you have kids you’re trying to keep them alive and in proximity while keeping them fed and hydrated enough to actually have fun on vacation...It’s hell week for your phone and still, it just needs to work.</quote>
    <link>https://techcrunch.com/2017/10/31/review-the-iphone-x-goes-to-disneyland/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>iPhone X Review: Face The Future</title>
    <quote>After months of hype, endless speculation, and a wave of last-minute rumors about production delays, the iPhone X is finally here. Apple says it’s a complete reimagining of what the iPhone should be, 10 years after the original revolutionized the world. That means some fundamental aspects of the iPhone are totally different here — most notably, the home button and fingerprint sensor are gone, replaced by a new system of navigation gestures and Apple’s new Face ID unlocking system. These are major changes.</quote>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/2017/10/31/16579748/apple-iphone-x-review</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
  	<title>iPhone X: (Review for Humans)</title>
  	<quote>The all-screen experience is mostly wonderful (even with that controversial notch), Simply put: Face ID is really f'ing impressive. But that’s because it’s invisible.</quote>
  	<link>https://youtu.be/mj0yn11vUOM</link>
  	<link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/nicolenguyen/iphone-x-review</link>
  </entry>

 
  
</feed>
