<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>November 17, 2017</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>First Digital Pill Approved to Worries About Biomedical ‘Big Brother’</title>
    <quote>For the first time, the Food and Drug Administration has approved a digital pill — a medication embedded with a sensor that can tell doctors whether, and when, patients take their medicine.</quote>
    <link>https://nyti.ms/2jrHlAN</link>
  </entry>
  
 <entry>
    <title>Amish Mutation Protects Against Diabetes and May Extend Life</title>
    <quote>Amish people living in a rural part of Indiana have a rare genetic mutation that protects them from Type 2 diabetes and appears to significantly extend their life spans, according to a new study.</quote>
    <link>https://nyti.ms/2jsw96P</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Yale Professors Race Google and IBM to the First Quantum Computer</title>
    <quote>Three giants of the tech world — Google, IBM, and Intel — are using a method pioneered by Mr. Schoelkopf, a Yale University professor, and a handful of other physicists as they race to build a machine that could significantly accelerate everything from drug discovery to artificial intelligence.</quote>
    <link>https://nyti.ms/2jnw4RW</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>What designers can learn from the iPhone X</title>
    <quote>1. Turning a constraint into a feature, 2. Making technology human, 3. Towards a gesture driven future.</quote>
    <link>https://uxdesign.cc/what-designers-can-learn-from-the-iphone-x-2b6f866443f3</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Thinking About Design Thinking</title>
    <quote>I had a great morning convo with my Automattic Design colleague Mike Shelton that took me down the rabbit hole of successive Google image searches for design thinking and design sprinting diagrams</quote>
    <link>https://maeda.pm/2017/11/13/thinking-about-design-thinking/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
</feed>
