<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>September 23, 2016</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Freeze-Dried Molecules Can Be Used to Whip Up Medicines Anywhere</title>
    <quote>Just add water. That’s the appeal of a new freeze-dry method that turns DNA and other molecules into small reaction pellets needed to make a wide range of pharmaceuticals. With freeze-dried molecular machinery portable enough to tote around in a suitcase, it could be possible to make drugs in remote places like developing countries, military outposts, and even outer space.</quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/602448/freeze-dried-molecules-can-be-used-to-whip-up-medicines-anywhere/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Salesforce Buying Twitter Would Make Perfect Sense</title>
    <quote>As for Salesforce, well, it already tried to buy LinkedIn (Microsoft got it), so it clearly wants a social network. It offers customer service software, market research tools, email marketing systems, and other products. Many of them already use social media. If you’ve ever tweeted a complaint about a company and received a response post-haste, you’ve seen how social networks play into Salesforce’s plans. Bringing Twitter in-house would facilitate building tools that connect sales, marketing and customer service clients directly to Twitter, providing deeper integration with its products.</quote>
    <link>https://www.wired.com/2016/09/salesforce-acquire-twitter/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Oracle’s Cloudy Future</title>
    <quote>Oracle’s lock on its existing customers, including the vast majority of the largest companies and governments in the world, remains very strong. And to that end its strategy of basically replicating its on-premise business in the cloud (or even moving its cloud hardware on-premise) makes total sense; it’s the same sort of hybrid strategy that Microsoft is banking on. Give their similarly old-fashioned customers the benefit of reducing their capital expenditures (increasing their return on invested capital) and hopefully buy enough time to adapt to a new world where users actually matter and flexible and focused clouds are the best way to serve them.</quote>
    <link>https://stratechery.com/2016/oracles-cloudy-future/</link>
  </entry>


  
  <entry>
    <title>Customer Service Bots Are Getting Better at Detecting Your Agitation</title>
    <quote>"[Humans] change our behavior in reaction to how whoever we are talking to is feeling or what we think they’re thinking,” says William Mark, who leads SRI International's Information and Computing Sciences Division. “We want systems to be able to do the same thing."</quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/602352/customer-service-bots-are-getting-better-at-detecting-your-agitation/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why Email Refuses to Die</title>
    <quote>And as long as society demands we officially introduce ourselves before asking for something or offering up something, we’ll need email. As long as individuals are allowed to set the context for interaction rather than jumping blindly into it, email will be around. And when we need to clearly and expansively lay out an idea without immediately inviting the input of others, email is there for us. If anything, email still survives because it protects us from interaction. It slows things down and forestalls online life.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/startup-grind/why-email-refuses-to-die-5fcb1272d5ff#.2m9vv076a</link>
  </entry>
  

  
</feed>
