<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>August 21, 2020</date>

  <entry>
    <title>Remote Work Is Reshaping San Francisco, as Tech Workers Flee and Rents Fall</title>
    <quote>Tech corporations are giving their staff extra freedom to work from anyplace. Staff are taking them up on the choice to relocate, forming the beginnings of a shift that might reshape not solely the Bay Space, but in addition the cities the place these tech employees are making new properties.</quote>
    <link>https://apkmetro.com/remote-work-is-reshaping-san-francisco-as-tech-workers-flee-and-rents-fall/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Why a Slack Backlash Is Inevitable</title>
    <quote>Workplace chat can amplify corporate infighting, help divide companies like social media divides countries, and facilitate employee organizing. Top executives, not employees, sign the checks for these services. And though they’re unlikely to get rid of them, many will inevitably crack down on their freewheeling nature.</quote>
    <link>https://bigtechnology.substack.com/p/why-a-slack-backlash-is-inevitable</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>A college kid’s fake, AI-generated blog fooled tens of thousands. This is how he made it.</title>
    <quote>It was meant as a fun experiment. But then one of his posts reached the number-one spot on Hacker News. Few people noticed that his blog was completely AI-generated. Some even hit “Subscribe.”</quote>
    <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/2020/08/14/1006780/ai-gpt-3-fake-blog-reached-top-of-hacker-news</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Apple, Epic, and the App Store</title>
    <quote>Indeed, this is the most frustrating aspect of this debate: Apple consistently acts like a company peeved it is not getting its fair share, somehow ignoring the fact it is worth nearly $2 trillion precisely because the iPhone matters more than anything.</quote>
    <link>https://stratechery.com/2020/apple-epic-and-the-app-store/</link>
  </entry>
</feed>
