<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>June 17, 2022</date>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Facebook Is Receiving Sensitive Medical Information from Hospital Websites</title>
    <quote>A tracking tool installed on many hospitals’ websites has been collecting patients’ sensitive health information—including details about their medical conditions, prescriptions, and doctor’s appointments—and sending it to Facebook.</quote>
    <link>https://themarkup.org/pixel-hunt/2022/06/16/facebook-is-receiving-sensitive-medical-information-from-hospital-websites</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why cryptocurrencies have gone from the next hot thing to a full-on meltdown</title>
    <quote>"The crypto house is on fire, and everyone is just rushing to the exits because there is a complete loss of confidence in the space,"</quote>
    <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/06/17/1105343423/cryptocurrencies-winter-crash-bitcoin-celcius</link>
  </entry>

 <entry>
    <title>For hundreds of years, the remarkable Vicente Lusitano has been forgotten. But now, finally, both his music and his story are being heard once more</title>
    <quote>What exactly appeals, then, about Lusitano's music? "Fundamentally, it’s just really beautiful," says McCleery. "There are very long arching phrases that seem to spin out into eternity. </quote>
    <link>https://www.bbc.com/culture/article/20220615-the-lost-16th-century-black-composer-vicente-lusitano/</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Tony Fadell: iPhone, iPod, Nest, Steve Jobs, Design, and Engineering</title>
    <quote>ony Fadell is an engineer and designer, co-creator of the iPod, iPhone, Nest Thermostat, and author of the new book Build: An Unorthodox Guide to Making Things Worth Making. </quote>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4oDZyOf6CW4</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Technical solutions to tackle AI bias</title>
    <quote>Bad algorithms can make life inconvenient for particular groups. Or they can be downright harmful.</quote>
    <link>https://monadical.com/posts/algorithm-bias.html</link>
  </entry>

 
  
</feed>
