<feed>
  <title>Friday Feed</title>
  <date>September 22, 2017</date>
  
  
 <entry>
    <title>Cells programmed like computers to fight disease</title>
    <quote>Cells can be programmed like a computer to fight cancer, influenza, and other serious conditions – thanks to a breakthrough in synthetic biology by the University of Warwick.  New research has discovered that a common molecule - ribonucleic acid (RNA), which is produced abundantly by humans, plants and animals - can be genetically engineered to allow scientists to program the actions of a cell.</quote>
    <link>https://www2.warwick.ac.uk/newsandevents/pressreleases/cells_programmed_like/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Satya Nadella Rewrites Microsoft’s Code</title>
    <quote>Nadella has not only restored Microsoft to relevance; he’s generated more than $250 billion in market value in just three and a half years... 
    How Nadella turned things around comes back to the book he had his top lieutenants read, and the culture that took hold from there. He has inspired the company’s 124,000 employees to embrace what he calls “learn-it-all” curiosity (as opposed to what he describes as Microsoft’s historical know-it-all bent) that in turn has inspired developers and customers—and investors—to engage with the company in new, more modern ways. Nadella is a contemporary CEO able to emphasize the kinds of soft skills that are often derided in the cutthroat world of corporate politics but are, in today’s fast-moving marketplace, increasingly essential to outsize performance.</quote>
    <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/40457458/satya-nadella-rewrites-microsofts-code</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Ready or Not, Facial Recognition is Here to Stay</title>
    <quote>Facial recognition is creeping its way into daily life. Learn how different industries, from travel to retail, are innovating with facial recognition.</quote>
    <link>https://verypossible.com/blog/ready-or-not-facial-recognition-is-here-to-stay</link>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>You might use AI, but that doesn’t mean you’re an AI company</title>
    <quote>As AI rises in popularity, there are a slew of businesses new and old looking to market themselves as “AI companies.” But Andrew Ng, one of the founders of the Google Brain team and a luminary in the space, said that there’s more to being an AI company than just using a neural net</quote>
    <link>https://venturebeat.com/2017/09/19/you-might-use-ai-but-this-doesnt-mean-youre-an-ai-company/</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Escaping e-mail hell</title>
    <quote>So, how can you stop having inbox-zero FOMO, get your points across succinctly, and save your marriage? Read on.</quote>
    <link>https://medium.com/the-year-of-the-looking-glass/escaping-e-mail-hell-f55905f3862f</link>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <quote></quote>
    <link></link>
  </entry>
</feed>
