<feed>
<title>Friday Feed</title>
<date>May 29, 2015</date>

<entry>
<title>Robotic pills to treat diabetes and arthritis</title>
<link>http://thestack.com/robotic-pills-novartis-treat-diabetes-arthritis-270515</link>
<quote>The drug delivery platform developed by Rani administers “large-molecule” drugs without the need for needles. Insulin for diabetes patients and other injectable drugs, such as treatments for rheumatoid arthritis, psoriasis and multiple sclerosis, would be made available for the first time as oral medicine.</quote>
</entry>

<entry>
<title>This Scientist Is Using Bacteria to Detect Cancer — and For His Latest Art Project</title>
<quote>Bioengineer Tal Danino is working out how to instruct bacteria to enter cancerous tumors — where it can detect and treat the disease noninvasively. And when Danino isn’t tinkering with bacteria’s healing potential, he makes artwork with it. He told us more about bacteria and how the artistic process drives his scientific research.</quote>
<link>https://medium.com/ted-fellows/this-scientist-is-using-bacteria-to-detect-cancer-and-for-his-latest-art-project-4405605cf643</link>
</entry>

<entry>
<title>Smartphones: A Better Approach To Clinical Trials</title>
<quote>The researcher can design something far more complex than a week-long diary study. They can use geolocation to track the patient’s movement over the week, trigger questions to check the patient’s well-being, and include an ongoing intervention sheet for patient-reported outcomes. The researcher can receive updates and track the patient with these in-the-moment insights. This allows them to understand the entire picture</quote>
<link>https://medium.com/@evan_trafford/smartphones-a-better-approach-to-clinical-trials-e2717c7a6f0c</link>
</entry>

<entry>
<title>KPMG Internet Trends 2015</title>
<link>http://kpcbweb2.s3.amazonaws.com/files/90/Internet_Trends_2015.pdf?1432738078</link>
<quote>KPCB’s Mary Meeker presents the 2015 Internet Trends report, 20 years after the inaugural “The Internet Report” was first published in 1995. Since then, the number of Internet users has risen from 35 million in 1995 to more than 2.8 billion today. The 2015 report looks at key Internet trends globally – while still healthy Internet user and smartphone subscription growth continue to slow, Internet engagement continues to rise led by consumers spending more time on their mobile devices, where they can be connected 24/7.</quote>
</entry>

<entry>
  <title>What Google Just Announced Is a Bombshell</title>
  <quote>The company demoed a new feature of its Android OS which allows its Now service (a dashboard of notifications focused on your life and interests) to plug in as a layer that essentially hovers above any app running on your phone or tablet. Activated by the home button, it's always there. This means that you can get contextual search information around almost anything you're doing, provided there is text and data that Google can pull from the app itself.</quote>
  <link>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2015-05-28/what-google-just-announced-is-a-bombshell</link>
</entry>

<entry>
<title>Jony Ive promoted to ‘Chief Design Officer,’ handing off managerial duties July 1st</title>
<quote>I have exciting news to share with you today. I am happy to announce that Jony Ive is being promoted to the newly created position of Chief Design Officer at Apple.</quote>
<link>http://9to5mac.com/2015/05/25/jony-ive-chief-design-officer/</link>
</entry>

<entry>
<title>Web vs. native: let’s concede defeat</title>
<quote>I feel we’ve gone too far in emulating native apps. Conceding defeat will force us to rethink the web’s purpose and unique strengths — and that’s long overdue.</quote>
<link>http://www.quirksmode.org/blog/archives/2015/05/web_vs_native_l.html</link>
</entry>

<entry>
<title>“Quartz is an API”: The path ahead for the business site that’s reshaping digital news</title>
<quote>“So when we say Quartz is an API, we don’t mean publish once and send it everywhere. We mean Quartz can go anywhere our readers are, in whatever form is appropriate.”</quote>
<link>http://www.niemanlab.org/2015/05/quartz-is-an-api-the-path-ahead-for-the-business-site-thats-reshaping-digital-news/</link>
</entry>

<entry>
<title>Google announces cut-down Android-based “Brillo” for Internet of Things</title>
<quote>At its I/O conference today, Google announced its entry into the Internet of Things (IoT) market with a pair of offerings: Brillo, an Android-derived operating system for IoT devices, and Weave a communications layer for IoT devices.</quote>
<link>http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2015/05/google-announces-cut-down-android-based-brillo-for-internet-of-things/</link>
</entry>

<entry>
<title>A follow-up (disambiguation? expansion? context?) regarding The Web of Alexandria.</title>
<quote>The "web" is an infrastructural system that was built by people, and it was built very recently and very sloppily. It currently has the property that it forgets what must be remembered, and remembers what must be forgotten</quote>
<link>http://worrydream.com/TheWebOfAlexandria/2.html</link>
<link>http://worrydream.com/TheWebOfAlexandria/</link>
</entry>



</feed>
